Hey!
What's up?
It is I, the Animal Well player.
He has arrived to play Animal Well for you.
Ah, that's a lie.
It's for me.
Well, mostly.
I do it for you, too.
How's it going?
Favorite Animal Well streamer.
I don't think there's a lot of them.
This game seems to be a little underground, you know?
Like, not many people know about it.
Uh, what day is it today?
Wednesday.
What are you all up to?
Animal Wellington?
That sounds delicious.
I would eat that.
Uh, Oliver is, uh, Oliver is well called Brun in Danish as well.
It is!
Except, uh, with a D at the end, instead of an N.
People know about it?
Yeah, but do, do you think people know about it?
Because your circle of friends and the places you go on the internet know about it, so to you it seems like everyone knows about it.
When in reality, not many people know about it.
If you think about the amount of people that live on planet Earth, and how many sales this game has had, If you calculate that percentage, probably almost nobody knows about this game.
Statistically speaking.
Frequency bias.
Yeah, something like that.
Hey, thank you, Ren, for subscribing.
Ren5792.
Thank you very much.
Is that a reference to Star Wars or something?
Kylo Ren?
Eh, maybe not.
And Crowwater and Roy as well.
Roy is at 18 months now.
Crowwater at 17 months.
Closely following.
Vapidraven, too.
18 months.
Thank you, Anonymous.
I appreciate it.
Whoa!
Hi, hi!
What's up, Armageddon girl?
Only 10k reviews?
It's certainly no Terraria.
How many reviews does Terraria have?
I know that game is quite popular.
And not everyone leaves a review, you know?
Like, I usually don't.
I just play the games.
And then I recommend them to my friends if I like them.
1.3 million?
Damn.
That's a lot.
What you see in your window?
Uh... nothing.
Because the curtains are pulled.
Or drawn.
I don't know what the...
correct...
term is.
We need a zoo stream!
To know our animals.
What?
Why?
What do you mean?
I can teach you if you want.
I'm walking home from the store.
Can you wait 10 minutes before starting?
Yeah, yeah, okay.
We're taking a 10 minute break, guys.
Don't worry, I'll probably spend 10 minutes reorienting myself anyway.
You'll be fine.
How did the animals get in the well?
Sea Tomato is out here asking the real questions.
Why are they in the well?
That's what we should be asking ourselves.
Why are the animals in there?
Who put them there?
Why is... why is there a well?
Well, that's a...
Well, that's an easy question.
Someone needed groundwater.
Duh!
Maybe they fell in.
Little Timmy?
I don't know who Little Timmy is.
Oh, is that the guy from Minecraft?
What is a well?
You know what?
Beats me.
I don't know.
Honestly, I don't understand wells.
Like in real life.
You dig a hole and then suddenly you have clean water?
That doesn't make sense to me.
Isn't there dirt in the hole?
I don't want to drink dirty water.
What the fuck?
Doesn't make any sense?
But that's me not knowing how wells work.
Ha ha ha ha!
Like, have you ever thought about it?
It doesn't make any sense?
Is there a water cleaning facility down there?
The government keeps all the good water deep underground.
Yeah, yeah.
I know there's such a thing called groundwater, but it's in the ground!
Isn't there like, fucking insects and dirt and viruses and shit?
You're right, I don't know wells well.
The only well I know is HG well.
That's the closest to a well I'm gonna get.
Groundwater?
How did they manage to grind it?
Ha ha ha ha!
Exactly.
That's a good one.
I didn't think about that one.
That's, that's nice.
But no microplastics at least?
Are you sure?
That stuff is everywhere nowadays.
It's probably on your forehead right now.
There's a bit of microplastic right on your forehead.
You need to go back to school to learn the water cycle?
Maybe.
Maybe I do.
I also need to go back to school to learn, uh, colors.
Because apparently I can't beat first grade.
If you know, you know.
Ha ha ha ha!
An anim- what do you mean animals?
Listen, I said this before.
Like Feynman said, it doesn't matter what you call an animal, okay?
It's just a name.
What matters is the function.
What does the animal do?
That's the important part.
And I know all about that.
Chinchillas, I got it.
Sugar gliders, wallabies, ferrets, fucking copypastas.
I know all about them.
I know what they do, how they poop, how they, you know, recreate and all that.
Yeah, the rodent animal.
You know what I mean?
The big rodent.
But you don't know your colors and blueprints.
Of course!
We have blue.
And... red.
Right?
By the way, I had a... somewhat of a realization.
Earlier today.
Because I was trying to think, what did I do last time in Animal Will, right?
Just to get my mind primed for gaming.
And I was like, wait a minute.
I got all four of the, um, flames.
Alright?
And then I had a thought.
Fuck, did I actually just cliffhanger right before credits or something?
I'm hoping there's more.
Meaning, uh, the game opens up.
Don't tell me anything, of course, but...
I'm really sorry in advance if I accidentally cliffhangered right before the end of the game.
I didn't even think about it.
You'll have to find out, I guess?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll find out.
I mean, I was...
I'm planning to play Animal Well for at least three hours today.
So I'm playing Animal Well for three hours.
At least.
Okay?
You can't stop me.
Even if I have to...
You know...
Invade all your minds and curse you all with my...
Backtracking.
Don't worry, you won't find everything in three hours.
Pah!
Watch me.
Watch me 100% this game in three hours.
Easy.
It's not even that big, this game.
At least it doesn't look like it.
Clueless?
No, you.
You're clueless.
My streamer.
My commenter.
My viewer.
What's going on, the not Greek, not Brit?
Wait, what are you then?
You must be something in between.
So that would mean...
You would be Swiss.
Isn't that somewhere in between?
No, French is way too west.
No?
In between those two countries?
What's my favorite animal?
I don't really have one.
I think now...
Cats.
Because I have a cat.
So now...
I'm obligated to say it's my favorite animal.
She's listening.
But really, my favorite animals are not cats.
No, no, nothing.
Never mind.
Southeast?
Yeah, Jackie's my favorite animal.
What's your favorite smell?
Uh...
That's a good question.
Huh.
What is my favorite smell?
Smell.
Wow.
You know what?
Probably, uh...
Garlic and chili.
In...
In olive oil.
On a pan.
Being heated.
Fuck me, that's good.
That is like...
Priming my...
Pavlovian responses to get ready for food.
You know?
Like, I'm salivating.
Just thinking of it.
What are you guys' favorite smell?
Animal smell.
Hahaha.
What's my favorite elementary particle?
Um...
Probably electrons.
Simply because they, uh...
They provide the means for me to play this game right now.
Then again, so do all the others.
But, you know.
You know what I mean.
Play re-animal after this?
Um...
Particle tier list?
Huh.
What is the most...
I mean...
Quarks are fucking S tier.
You wouldn't have anything without the quarks, right?
Easy.
Everything else is in B.
I can answer that right now.
Sulfur is obviously S tier.
Is it?
That's not an elementary particle.
That's a molecule, my dude.
What about the different types of quarks?
No, no, they're all equal.
I...
I love them all like I love my children.
B is for bar...
Barticle?
Hmm.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
There's something on my foot.
Oh.
It was a piece of hair.
In my sock.
It was on my foot.
It was so weird.
It's gone now.
How many children exactly?
Uh, one.
I don't believe in quarks.
Me neither, man.
Me neither.
All that science...
Makes no sense.
If I can't see it with my own two eyes...
It doesn't exist.
How many socks do you wear?
Actually, two right now.
Two socks and they're heated.
I have my heated socks on for the first time.
Since last year.
I don't have a basement.
I mean, that's what I officially say.
Unofficially?
Well...
Why heated?
Because I need heat.
I thought that would be obvious.
My feet are cold, okay?
I have bad blood circulation down below in my feet.
Two pairs.
One on each.
Actually, yeah!
I do have two pairs of socks on right now.
I have normal socks.
That's the first layer.
And then I have my, uh...
Heated socks.
Second layer.
And those are on the lowest setting.
And then on top of that, I'm wearing shoes right now as well.
As to retain the heat.
That's being produced by the socks.
Meaning I can keep the heat level on minimum.
Waste minimum energy.
And keep my feet warm.
I know I'm weird.
Your feet stinks, right?
If I sit in these shoes all day with this, then yeah.
Then you gotta wash both feet and the socks.
Of course.
It becomes like an animal smell.
Yeah, my feet are toasty right now.
Roasty and toasty.
Wearing my freezer socks?
That sounds horrible.
God damn.
Okay.
Well, I think it's time we play some Animal Well.
Because I can't listen to this music forever.
I'm getting too hyped!
Let me do this.
Is it working?
It is.
Put this on this one and then click this button.
Whoop!
Look at that.
I may actually take my clothes off.
One sec.
Because when your feet are hot, the rest of your body also becomes hot.
So now I'm only wearing socks.
I'm kidding.
I had a jacket on that I took off.
I'm the kind of weirdo that insists on saving money everywhere so I don't even have heat on.
Because when you keep your feet heated, it doesn't matter.
The rest of your body can stay as cold as it needs to be, you know?
Maybe I lied about that just now.
You'll never know.
So, guys, check it out.
I cliffhangered right here.
Whoops.
Wait, what is the button?
Oh, here.
I got four flames, but I didn't put the last flame in yet.
So, uh...
You know, let's put it in.
And it's actually, uh, this one.
I knew it.
A new area is opening up.
Thank god.
Something goes in slot.
Uh, I need to...
Hold on, I need to really quickly, um...
I'm not gonna die a single time today, by the way.
Because I know this game so well now, I'm good at it.
Uh, we have the slinky.
Grab that.
I just wanna quickly...
Oh yeah, this one!
This one is sick!
I'm gonna be pinging everything.
No fireworks.
Let me play the song of my people.
Oh, we're so back.
Okay.
And this one?
We're gonna use this everywhere we see suspicious dirt.
Okay?
Eat that.
And of course the disc.
And this stuff.
Let me remind myself how to do this.
That's right.
Okay!
Um, what do you...
I didn't want to go down there.
Are you ready?
What's down here?
Looks like we got some animalistic probabilities in the air.
Those will surely, uh...
ruin my day.
At some point.
Oh, I love the ambiance.
This is a little creepy.
Is there a server rack somewhere here?
Would you...
Oh, I didn't even see those guys on the right.
Maybe I can heal up.
I did say I wasn't gonna die today, so let's just...
Play it safe.
I'm going back up.
Call me crazy, but...
I saw some food.
I think.
I...
Did not see food.
Never mind.
Okay, back down.
Oh!
Also!
We should be doing this.
That, and...
This.
I just need to see the suspicious dirt again.
One more time, you know?
And then I'll forever log onto it.
Never forget.
Okay.
What is this animal animal?
It's the starfish!
Right?
At least some kind...
It's like a merge between a starfish and...
A normal fish.
But seen from the front.
Really weird design.
Maybe they're running animal experiments down here.
Maybe that's what the animal well is.
Because...
The animals were imprisoned, right?
Someone did that!
There's an evil person somewhere here.
Jump!
What am I doing?
Oh!
I see, I see.
Okay.
I understand.
Let's just try that one more time.
In fact, I have an idea.
Ah, damn.
I can't.
Ah!
I almost did it!
That was so close.
Again.
Go!
Yeah!
The master is back.
Why is it so dark?
Whoa, what is this effect?
My light isn't working.
Call the authorities.
Oh my god, this is...
Wait, it's almost like there's some kind of black tar.
More.
In the front.
That's a church mouse.
Statue of it, at least.
What's happening?
Another one.
Oh!
Secret found!
I think.
It's actually kind of a cool way to test the...
Oh!
To test the waters ahead with this spinning top.
You know, you can check if anything is destructible and if anything is safe.
This bird is gonna ruin my day.
Can't get in there.
Oh, I can't get there either, but I can get up here.
I see a button.
Oh, this place is scary looking.
Oh, there... I didn't even...
Look!
That... that wall right there?
Right here!
It's almost impossible to see.
Am I crazy?
It blends in so well.
With the environment.
I'm going really slow.
Am I hearing moaning?
Oh, no.
Oh!
Shit!
Is that a wall?
It is a wall.
Okay.
What is that?
I don't like it.
Can we firecrack you?
Are you gonna follow me if I drop down?
Dude, I'm so scared.
I can't do this.
Oh!
I'm dead!
I can't move!
This way!
Oh, boy!
I hate when they follow me!
Stop!
Hey, you like music?
You hate music.
Ugh!
Please no more chase sequences.
Ah!
Okay, nice, nice, nice.
We got a shortcut.
Save the game.
Save the damn game.
Okay.
Oh, I can't get up there.
I can't get up there.
Okay, so prediction time?
I will unlock something that will nullify this threat.
I mean, obviously, given what we're seeing here, but...
Ah!
Chess spotted!
I see you there.
But how do I enter?
Let me put a chess symbol.
There we go.
Never forgetty.
Rest in pepperonis or something.
I didn't mean to throw that!
I wasted it.
Oh, oh!
This spot right here!
Yeah!
Oh!
I know who I am!
Very hidden!
Let's call this...
What is this animal?
I don't even know.
I think it's a flulhest.
It's a seahorse.
No, a river horse.
I don't know what the English word is.
Um...
Let's just write, uh, S.
Or, actually, R.
R.
And then...
Here.
Okay.
Now we got bad guys down there.
The background looked like, uh, red and blue lights.
As in...
Red and blue lights in a computer.
You know?
Like, status...
Status lights.
Or something.
Also, I still have to experiment with this, um...
Pinging system.
Like, does it matter where I am on the screen?
Will it always reveal everything if I'm up here?
Down in the bottom right or something?
That's what I need to test.
Ooh, I like the design on this place.
It's like I...
You know what this reminds me of?
On Windows 10 or something, there's like a high contrast theme.
That you could activate.
It's always...
A little bit weird looking, but it looks like this.
I see.
Okay.
Ah...
Wait, what?
I see.
It's a gauntlet.
Then I get up there and I...
What do I do up there?
I throw a disc.
No, there's vines.
Let's...
Let me see here.
So I run to the left.
I jump down.
I go through.
Ah!
I throw the disc through!
Of course.
That's it.
So we do this one and then...
One, two, three.
Up you go!
Oh.
Well, hold on a minute then.
I...
Don't know.
Let me go up here.
Oh, I'm here now.
Oh, I can't get back down!
I fucked up!
Wait, are they...
Is their vision based on sound?
Doesn't look like it.
I could go top left.
I don't want to go through this place.
I hate these guys.
If you like this...
Follow it!
Oh, they're only moving when I'm moving!
Yeah!
Fucking run!
Suck it!
Wow, no reaction!
Oh god, oh god!
Okay, we're safe.
Oh, I hate those animal thingies.
What if I were to do this?
Alright.
Just falls off.
There's a skull right here underneath the church mouse.
Okay, so let me think about this.
The vines are blocking my disc.
So either we get rid of the vines somehow, or we need to somehow press both of those buttons at the same time.
We can't throw more than one disc at a time.
Can I somehow with my...
yo-yo...
do something?
Or maybe...
this one.
Do we have a receiver anywhere?
But hold on a second.
There's also a button...
down there.
Let me quickly take a look at this again.
Okay, so where is it going exactly?
It goes to down there.
And then it stops, because we need to open that.
And that's a square, and the square is on the left!
I see.
But to get to the square, we need to open...
the cross, which is the one in the center.
So we do need to do this first.
Somehow.
Um...
Yeah.
What's going on with that?
I guess I can...
walk through here.
Let me just try this again.
Yeah.
So that's...
Oh!
I see.
I understand now.
I get it.
It briefly opened.
I didn't notice that before.
Ah, but shit, I can't go back now.
Oh no!
So I gotta go here again.
There's gotta be a way to distract these dudes.
No?
Maybe not.
Hey!
Oh yeah!
God, I hate them.
Oh, oh no, no.
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead.
It's over.
I'm okay.
Quick, quick, quick!
Ah!
One HP.
We are in trouble.
No more silly mistakes.
Also!
Can't fool me.
No sir.
Also, let's just keep an eye- Oh!
Charge Pals!
Huh?!
You can't do anything!
Fuck me, that was scary!
God, I hate when I get chased!
Please no more chases.
I wanna relax!
Aw, man.
This is, uh, like, solving puzzles when things are scary?
That's the combo that breaks me.
That's why I had so much trouble with puzzles in Silent Hill, and Amnesia, the Dark Descent, at least when I played it.
It's just, I can't think straight when that happens, you know?
Anyways, we're back here now, so we can try this new strategy.
One, two, three.
Go!
What happens then?
No!
Oh no, we needed to hit the- Uh, the button below me here.
But how?
Oh!
Oh, we made it!
Hey!
Thought I had to redo it all.
Nice.
Very nice!
Now we can go here and jump in that, that opens...
One of three, okay.
But I don't wanna go that way, yet.
What if I were to jump here?
What then, eh?
Oh no!
Go...
Bow bow bow bow bow bow bow bow bow geb Co, go go go go!
We take no damage.
Jump, jump, jump, jump, jump!
We're fine.
Phew.
Ok, we got the 2 HP, we can try the Church Mouse Route.
one more.
So wait, how am I gonna?
It's coming already!
It's over.
See ya, bitch.
Dumbass.
Nice!
Okay, two out of three.
And the last button is up top, it seems.
To get there, I would need to arrive from above.
Yeah, so we go in here and we go up left.
Oh god, I have one HP.
Go!
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck you.
We're in trouble.
Are you gonna come after me?
I'm not sure what I'm supposed to do here.
Shit!
No, no, no, no, no.
Back in, back in.
Fuck that noise.
Wait, there's something up on the left?
Oh, it's a firecracker.
Are they supposed to work against these dudes?
Oh yeah, kinda.
These, yeah.
It's working.
So, I wanna go, get to the ladder now.
Get to the ladder.
Climb!
Okay.
Very good.
Okay, I see vines up there, so there's a secret path.
And to get there, maybe... I think I see it, actually.
Yeah.
Top left, top left.
I'm gonna use a firecracker.
Can you not, like, do that?
Whatever you're doing right there?
Please stop.
Please don't do it.
I have one HP.
I can't throw the firecracker while on the ladder.
It's really unfortunate.
Come on.
Come on, you see me.
Come to me.
You don't want to?
I could jump straight down.
Go left.
Bubble to the left.
Up, right.
Do it!
Fuck it, go!
Ho, ho, ho, ho!
Woo!
I'm good.
That was sick.
Okay, now...
I don't think I see any...
Oh!
What was that?
I didn't even see it!
Fuck my heart!
Oh!
Please don't do that!
I don't know what happened!
How do I get back?
This way.
Fuck it.
Oh my god, I'm dying!
Just hurry.
I don't know what's happening here.
Just go.
Click this button.
Shit, shit.
What?
How do I...
Fuck!
This is impossible.
I don't know.
Okay, let that stay there.
Come here, buddy!
Come here!
That's right!
Jump on the button!
You jumped over it!
Yes!
Oh!
Yeah, yes!
I think we're good.
What?
Now?
I press that.
I fall down.
I fall down once.
And I jump up with the bubble.
Oh!
Wow!
What a fucking mess this is!
Lantern!
Oh!
Oh, shit!
Removes the bird!
How much you want to bet it also removes the bad guys in the dust ceiling?
Yeah, look!
They disperse.
Incredible.
Oh, this is so weird.
Look at them trying to close in on me.
I guess if I unequip this right now, I'm dead.
Yeah, they're back now.
That chest right there, though, is really something, isn't it?
I'm gonna try... Oh, I hope it removes these.
Hey, stay out of my way.
I got light.
Yeah, that's right!
Stay away!
Bastards!
Man, the animation is so creepily done on these guys.
It's something else.
So I see a path here.
But should I go for that?
Right now?
Or is there something else?
I can't see anything immediately.
So get down there.
We just go all the way down, okay?
Oh.
Oh!
Okay, you're a little bold, aren't you?
You still went for a swipe there.
You mind going away?
Thank you.
Check for secrets.
Oh yeah, this is it.
This is it.
Look at this.
This whole place is filled with these donuts.
It's donut time.
I really want to bring out my ping-ping.
But, uh, I'm gonna die if I do.
So I'm not gonna do it.
Is this whole place filled with them?
It is.
What is this place even?
Can I comfortably change my thing or do I die?
Like, how do I...
HOOP!
Crap!
Wait, are they only in the ceiling?
One.
Ooh, okay, okay.
I see.
Hold on, is it instant?
It's not... ins...
Okay, I'm safe here.
Okay, gotcha.
Nice.
Yo-yo time.
Okay, nothing on the scanner.
Really?
I can't do that?
Let me see here.
Okay, so I'm safe here.
Three out of four.
I don't like the scary face on the door.
Would you... oh, fuck.
I just ran into it like a dumbass.
How would I possibly get to the button underneath?
Dang.
That doesn't fall down.
But...
Now it worked?!
I have no clue.
Why that just decided to go all the way around.
When before it wouldn't.
I don't understand.
But sure, I mean, I was so sure I had to use that there.
What?
Not sure how I did it, but we did it.
One HP, ladies and gents.
And...
Are we safe here?
I don't see any enemies.
But...
I have a feeling this lantern is also gonna reveal other things.
Oh!
Prediction time!
Somewhere, this lantern will reveal more arrows.
To rescue animals.
The ferrets.
You know?
Go up.
Uh...
So we need one button for that.
That's presumably the yellow one.
And it looks like I have to come down from above.
Uh...
What was that?
No!
No, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Nope, nope.
Ew!
What the f...
Oh, shit!
That's it!
Stay away!
Where's the disc?!
That's right!
Stay away from me.
Cool music!
Oh god, look at his face!
Okay, looks like he's staying away.
Are you gonna follow me to the next screen?
I think he is.
Yep.
Oh, no.
Dude, I vibe with this music.
This slaps.
Stay away!
Foul menace!
He's moaning.
Oh, you're ugly!
What are you even?
Creature of the underworld.
What is my goal here?
I need to figure out something.
Let me go back this...
What's that?
The baseline just hit.
Oh shit, we're back here.
I guess I go through the door up there?
But I can't, I can't.
Shit.
One, two, three.
Okay, we...
Okay, we gotta ring around the Rosie a little bit here, I think.
Get away!
Away with you!
Actually, maybe bring him over here.
That's right, come over here.
Come here, buddy.
That's right, stay there.
Go!
Away!
Away, I say!
Oh.
What's up here?
Button?
One of four.
Okay, that activates the fan.
Progress.
Good.
Now we go back up, I guess.
So, one, two, three.
One, two, three!
I can't, I can't get up there.
He's gonna be on my ass.
I guess I go...
Lure him over here.
God, he's so...
Ugly.
Go.
Go, go, go.
One, two, three.
Away.
Stay away!
Stay the fuck away from me.
Uh, so what is the plan?
We ascend?
Uh, on a bubble.
Whoa!
What the...
Lasers?!
No way!
Fuck!
Okay.
I don't know how far back I am now.
Laser...
Oh, oh, oh!
It's happening immediately, I think.
Oh, I can turn it on and off!
I didn't realize.
Well, I think I did realize, but I didn't realize.
You know what I mean?
Um...
Where the hell was I?
Oh, I died there.
Uh, so we gotta go back down?
It's...
There's gotta be like a safe point down here that I missed.
Surely.
Okay, that opens...
Okay, he's not here.
Oof!
Wait, I gotta do the buttons again!
Oh, fuck that!
Oh, no.
Wait, this one is...
I'm confused.
Oh, no.
Get out!
So we gotta be super quick there.
Fuck off.
Stay away!
Don't you dare laser me up there.
Yo!
Wow!
See ya!
See ya, nerd!
Eat that!
Grab that!
Go down!
Button!
Opens that, okay.
Shit, shit, shit.
What now, what now, what now?
Button up above.
Don't you moan at me.
Uh...
Oh, shit, I see.
One, two, three.
One, two, three, four.
Okay, one, two, three, four.
Oh, shit, he tried to grab me.
Fuck, I fell down!
I accidentally deactivated the lamp!
Get away with me.
Ugh!
Let's go!
Button time!
That's two.
He's gonna laser...
Okay, okay, that's fine, that's fine.
You can do that.
If I fall down here, what then?
Oh, I guess I can't anymore.
This takes me back here?
That's not what I want.
I wanna go down here.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
One, two, three.
One, two, three, four.
Okay, one, two, three, four.
Come on, please don't fuck me up now.
One, two, three, four.
Yeah!
Lamb time!
You like the lamp, bitch!
Uh...
We need one more.
Right side.
We got this!
Right, so we gotta do this.
Uh...
To get there...
It's simple.
We lured this dude over here.
We've done it before.
That's right!
Stay in your corner!
One, two, three.
Yeah!
Away with you!
Woo!
Shit!
I'm dead!
Stay away!
Oh my god!
Where's my lantern?!
I got it!
Go, go, go!
Wait, what?
Oh yeah!
We gotta go through the door.
Okay, okay, okay.
Lure him over here.
There we go.
One, two, three.
I have full firecrackers or what?
Oh ho!
Don't laser me now!
Duh!
Come on!
What did I just open?
Here?
Yeah, here.
Oh, we got a rodent.
He's waiting in the top right.
I see you!
Don't you laser me.
What now?
What happens now?
Okay, okay.
Oh!
The fucking reflections!
Secret discovered.
Step on the skulls.
Open this.
BB wand!
Bridge babies!
Uh...
We go down quick.
Where's my lantern?!
Oh no, no!
I'm dead, I'm dead, I'm dead!
I'm dead!
What are the chances?!
I hate this guy!
Wait, everything is undone?!
There's no way, right?
What's happening?
Don't tell me I have to do it again!
Wait, where am I?
We gotta go down here.
Fuck.
By the way, first death doesn't count, so I'm good.
Oh, wait a minute.
What did I actually...
Oh, I still have it?!
Wait, what is the difference?
Have I always been able to do this, or is that new?
I don't remember?!
Have I always been able to...
I mean, I just...
Hmm...
I am not sure.
I think...
I'm able to make more bubbles.
Oh no, I gotta do this again!
Oh shit, we gotta remove this.
I can't read anything now.
Uh, let's just make a little error here.
Uh, slot.
Okay, so hold on a minute.
We died here.
There's obviously a path down here.
I...
Like, I can't think when I have a predator on my ass!
I just can't!
Also, what is...
Why do I need two bubbles?
I don't understand.
Do they provide multi...
Like...
Okay, yeah, I've not been able to do this before.
This is new.
What is the point of all these...
Like...
What is it good for?
I...
Ah, shit!
Man, I don't wanna do this again!
Are you kidding me?!
Ah...
Fuck, I thought I got through it, man!
Let me please get up there, before I lose my mind.
Thank you.
So, is this guy gonna appear again, or...
Oh, no.
Oh, noooo!
Where's the disc?
Okay, that one's done.
Uh...
Get away!
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh!
Oh!
Uh...
Don't you fucking laser me while I'm on the bubble!
Secret discovered!
Throne!
Incubator?
Don't incubate me!
Oh, God!
Uh...
I got hit!
Mayday!
Oh, crap!
Oh!
Fuck you!
Bro!
Fuck!
Where's the save point?!
God fucking damn it, man!
This is so difficult!
Please don't test my platforming shit while I'm scared as well, and being chased.
That I can't handle.
I gotta do all of this again.
We're fine!
What?!
Oh, I was flying!
Hahaha!
Okay, okay.
Uh...
Fuck you.
Oh...
Please get away from me.
Away!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Absolutely not.
Uh...
I go here again.
Don't, don't...
Don't you fucking do it.
Oh, sh...
Oh, his face is on the door!
We have to somehow do something to him.
And then, and then we can open this door.
Oh, crap.
God!
Oy, oy, oy, oy, oy, oy.
I wanna get up to the right.
No, don't you shoot at me.
I gotta lure him to the left.
Ah, crap.
And then we gotta go quick.
Come here, come here.
Oh, my God.
It's...
I'm dead.
Wow!
What the fuck am I supposed to do?
Uh...
Get up here.
Why, we gotta do this again?
See ya!
Oh, God.
Nope, no, no, no.
Okay, and then top right.
We have one HP.
There's no way we can do this.
Oh, wow.
You can't hit me down there.
No way.
Okay.
Not here, not here.
Uh, here we go.
One, two...
One, two, three, four.
Woo!
Okay, now we go over here.
And then we go through that door up there.
So we lure him to the right.
Don't laser me.
Okay, door's open, door's open.
Door is open.
What the fuck?
Okay, so what do I do?
What do I do?
Fuck.
Bro!
Fuck this game!
What is this bullshit?
We gotta do everything again!
I must be missing a save point.
There's no way this is intended.
There's just no way.
Where is this damn phone I'm missing?
Like, it's gotta be down here.
Also, if I turn...
Oh, okay, I instantly get...
Okay.
I thought maybe there was a safe spot in there with a little secret and shit.
But, uh, I guess not.
Bro, I don't wanna do this again!
Fuck!
Um...
Go.
Actually, uh, start with this.
Something's to the right.
I think.
Let me quickly make a mark.
Fucking...
There!
Ah!
Cuckoo!
That's one.
Uh, now we go...
One, two, three, four.
Oh, crap!
Aw, I missed it!
Okay, good.
Speed running.
One left.
Uh, actually two left.
Come here.
D'aw!
Stay away from me!
One, two, three, four.
There it is!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh...
Why did I go this way?
Oh!
No.
Down here now.
Okay, okay, uh...
Fuck.
No!
I can't believe I did that again.
Like, the firecrackers gotta have an effect on them.
Why else would they put them here?
Let me try and firecrack her here now.
Suck it!
Actually, yeah.
Uh...
Can I firecrack this?
It doesn't work!
Actually, it kinda does work.
Can I bubble this away or something?
Can I, can I...
Bubble wads!
Bubble, bubble, bubble!
Run!
Maybe I can refract the laser in my bubble!
Snell's Law!
Oh!
What's happening?
Damn!
Oh my god, the fireworks pretty!
Look at that!
I had a feeling!
But what about all the eggs?
Hey, that's cool!
I can move around with the...
Hold on, I wanna test something.
Oh, I can't change items.
Super tester.
Wow, Discord mods in the credits here.
Look at that.
D'aw!
No, thank you for making a game!
Oh!
House key?
Really?
Well, well, well!
Where's my house?
I get an apartment out of this!
That's a good deal.
What is the point of all these bubbles?
I don't understand what the point is of this.
I wanna find my house.
So there's something going on here.
Oh!
Look at this!
Smiley faces!
Just like the, um...
Oh god, I don't even...
I don't even have it open right now.
Let me actually do that.
I forgot to open this.
Um...
One sec.
Where did I have that?
Duh, duh, duh, duh, duh, duh.
Animal well.
Notes.
There we go.
Is that working?
There it is!
Boom.
Okay.
Um...
Let me see here.
One, two, three, four smiley faces.
Eight smiley faces in total.
What is this?
What the hell is this?
I think I need to play a tune and then this, uh...
Whatever this is.
The skulls will disappear.
Up here.
Maybe.
But where's my house?
I got a key.
That was my melody.
You like that?
Oh!
Maybe...
Oh, I thought for sure this would be it.
Might somehow...
Weird.
Okay.
Uh...
Let me mark a chest here.
Oh!
We can explore now without the boss!
Man.
My heart.
We can calmly explore now.
Check this out.
Okay.
Would've been cool though, right?
Uh...
I'm looking for...
Destructible ground.
Oh yeah, there's a colored wall there as well.
There's actually so much still.
Oh!
And let's not forget up here!
I can go there now because I have a lantern.
Yeah.
Which is here.
This place.
Oops.
Didn't mean to fall in the water.
But I kinda wanna stay down here a little bit longer.
Because I know there's a chest, uh...
Up here.
Ah, but I probably get to that...
From the other side.
That makes sense.
And...
There's a slot here for something.
Do we know of a spot that needs...
A key?
Okay.
Let's think about it.
Home?
We started the game...
Down here, didn't we?
Somewhere.
Maybe...
Uh, here.
Maybe that will work.
Oh, no, wait.
That was the, um...
The lights.
Oh.
Hold on a minute.
I just need to consider my options here for a bit.
Bear.
One.
Let's remove this.
We don't need that anymore.
Um...
Yeah.
This is a candidate for exploration.
Let's go do that now.
That's...
I think...
What was the entrance we used?
I think it was on the left.
And then...
Maybe all the way up here, actually.
No.
It was somewhere...
Here.
This one.
I think.
Or that one.
So we gotta go back to...
The X.
Which is bear one.
Um...
Before I do...
I wanna check this right here.
Oh my god.
There's no enemy right now.
It feels so good.
So calm, isn't it?
No scary music.
No ethereal being chasing me.
Oh!
Ha-ha!
Uh...
My thing is stuck.
Hey!
Stop!
Motherfucker!
Ah!
Glitch discovered!
Okay.
Never mind.
So...
There's a door here...
With the face of the evil creature.
Making a horrible buzzing sound.
Oh no, wait.
That's the fan.
I'm seeing destructible ground underneath it.
Oh god.
I'm making noise.
Oh!
Whoa!
Look at that!
Check it out!
That right there on the right side is...
Is that not destructible?
No!
Okay.
Whatever.
I can't hit that.
I guess it only works on stuff below.
There was also another door.
Wasn't there.
There was another door with that face on it.
It was here, I think.
No...
Was it?
Oh, wait!
Look at this!
Looks like there's a path down there.
Let me get back.
And on the way, I'm gonna check out...
Do I go top side first?
There's also this right here.
I think I go top side first.
Work it from top to bottom, right?
Yeah.
I also wanted to go here.
Just to see what was up there.
I couldn't do it because the monster was chasing me.
Oh wait, this is not even the way.
How did I get up there?
Oh, I guess I went from over here.
Yeah, yeah.
This was it.
Accelerate me.
It's too slow.
Okay.
I still don't know what's supposed to go in those receptacles over there.
You know, there's clearly like a little indentation or a slot for something.
Looks like something circular, but...
You know.
Something huge.
Like something that weighs a lot.
Something like...
Your mom.
Oh!
Incubator?
Isn't an incubator something to do with like...
Dinosaurs.
Right?
You incubate them...
And...
Then stuff happens.
Yeah.
Dinosaurs.
It's really...
Wait, there can't be nothing here.
I don't believe that.
No way.
No, wait.
Incubator is like...
So, to me it looks like a chair.
But now I'm also being reminded of...
You know, this...
Type of demon.
That will...
Seduce you or something.
You know?
Isn't that what that is?
It makes sense with the whole...
Devil spawn...
Theme here.
Ah!
There's the door!
I don't...
Understand.
Speak, friend, and you may enter.
Mello.
Oh!
Oh, but wait.
Okay, so I think...
New...
New theory.
We gotta open the other blue door, which would open this door.
Right?
Something like that.
Or...
Or maybe...
Okay, fine.
I'll be back.
Let me put a note.
This is going to be a...
Not that...
Oh, God.
People close the map.
Here we have a...
Door.
Wait.
Is there maybe a...
Symbol for that?
Eh...
Let's say...
This is a door now.
I'll never remember that.
Nonsense.
Of course I will.
Now, what is going on up here?
What if I were to fly?
Yeah!
Okay.
It's fine.
Let's keep exploring.
There are so many mysteries in this game, man.
Like, what the...
Hell is going on?
This can't be it up here.
I just refuse to believe it.
Like...
What?
I'm telling you, we can remove those dice at some point.
Okay, let's check out the rights...
Oh, I think I did that already.
So we can erase that.
Oh my God, please.
How do I erase?
That one.
Okay.
Oh!
Right, I wanted to go down.
There's a little path here.
For sure.
Whoops.
Didn't mean to do that.
Oh!
Wow.
Oh.
I got a TV!
Interesting.
Aha!
Save the game.
Locked.
Why is there a carrot?
Oh.
Is this gonna go...
Cuckoo!
Oh!
Stopwatch?
Where?
What?
Can I tell the...
I don't see my stopwatch.
Dude, what is happening here?
Wait, is this...
Does this mean I'm missing three items here, maybe?
I mean, not necessarily, I guess, but...
Could be.
The stopwatch is not showing up in my inventory.
Whoa.
Yo, that's a cool effect!
Look at that donut!
What did I say earlier?
Didn't I speak of donuts?
It's an ethereal donut.
Take me!
Wow, that's a really cool effect.
Man.
What the hell is going on?
In this...
Oh, I'm here.
I thought the bird turned into the big bird person when I turned on the lamp.
But he was always there in the back, just not illuminated.
That's funny.
Uh...
Okay.
Wait a minute.
Oh, you bastard.
Okay.
Ah, wait, wait, wait, I see something.
Check it out.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, yeah.
Yep.
Yep, yep, yep.
No secre...
Is that a Tamagotchi?
Pedometer!
Peacock figure!
An otter figure.
Oh, no.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wait a minute.
What?
Wait a second, then.
I mean...
I, I, I don't, I don't know what's, what's happening here.
Is this counting my total steps?
Dude.
What if I am actually a Tamagotchi, and someone out there is controlling me?
It's all...
It's a simulation.
Right?
You know what I mean?
That's funny.
Right.
Let me check up here again.
Whoa.
That's an elephant!
In the center.
Jackrabbit.
Bro, what is, what is this here?
Take me into the...
Yeah.
Don't want me!
Wait, something is beeping in it.
Disrupt the donut!
Very weird.
Yo, the, uh, spinning top is super slow here for some reason.
Look how fast it is in that direction.
Wait, what?
How did I do that?
Okay, I don't know how I just did that.
I can do, uh, spinning top tricks.
So I guarantee you, when this reaches, uh, one o'clock, it's gonna be a...
Cuckoo!
And maybe I wanna be here for that.
Oh god, I'm getting...
Ugh.
I'm getting reminded of something else.
If you know, you know.
I'm tired of being disappointed.
But I, I love this house.
It's cozy as hell.
Look at my little lamp up there.
Save the game.
What do I have in the back?
Is that a little picture of a mushroom?
There's bubbles in the air.
Is that a couch?
Look at this.
Oh, is that my girlfriend on the wall?
Can I watch something, uh...
Okay, so hold on.
I have an idea.
Check it out.
I figured out the puzzle.
This is the order, okay?
We gotta go sat face?
Alright, can you see my cursor?
I think you can, yeah.
Sat face?
Wait, there's multiple sat faces.
It's that one, okay.
Wait, we don't have that sat face.
It's not here.
Oh, that...
No, wait, what?
Is that the one?
Yeah, it is, it is.
Okay, so that one...
Followed by the...
Happy?
So we have...
Let me go check out this thing now.
I guarantee you something will happen.
Somehow.
Uh...
What was it here?
Oh, wait a minute!
Wait a minute!
I think I get it, I get it!
The clock!
It's a clock, this...
This is the clock.
So when time strikes 12, we have the sat face.
When time strikes 1, we have whatever face is hiding behind there.
Wait a minute.
Let's just see.
Oh no, the vines are in the way, I can't...
How do I remove the vines?
I guess I just do this.
What is it?
It's the angry face!
Okay, angry face.
Oh wait, this one resets.
Angry face!
Okay, so now...
Cuckoo!
Oh, it's gonna take a while.
Is this real time?
Ah, but wait a second.
There's way less...
Wait, there's all sorts of numbers here.
5, 2...
Then we have like counters.
0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0, 0...
Oh!
No, I don't get it.
Cuckoo!
Oh, hold on.
Oh!
No!
I'm sorry!
How long was that up?
I just saw a bunch of spam.
Out of the corner of my eye.
I couldn't have been that long.
Okay, let me explain what I did, okay?
I was over here.
I was jumping on the vines to see the face.
And the face...
Was the angry face, okay?
The face was the angry face.
And then I was here, and I went like, Cuckoo!
Cuckoo!
Then I went over here.
And then I looked at this clock, and I noticed there was a 5, a 2.
And all these doors here.
You see that?
There's 0, 0, 0.
And 0, 0, 0.
And 0, 0, 0, 0 here.
But what about the stopwatch I got?
Like...
What about that?
What?
Oh no.
Uh...
Wait a sec.
What is the significance of this?
Also, this is not my local time.
Because my local time is 1638.
So I don't know what kind of time this tracks.
Maybe from when you start, or lock into the game?
You know?
Anyway, uh...
Let me take a picture of this.
I was gonna show you what I meant here.
Um...
Don't worry, I'm never gonna forget to bring it back down again.
So...
There's some kind of melody going on here.
Oh yeah.
Actually.
Oh.
Wait a sec.
I have ideas now.
But let me just put this in here.
So...
Wait.
I tried playing this song, right?
Nothing happened.
Maybe I tried to play that song...
Either here...
Or near the other place with the smileys.
You know what I mean?
Let me do that.
Actually, let's try this here first.
I'm gonna have to open the notes while I do it.
Otherwise, I can't see, okay?
Uh...
Let me zoom in on this.
It's very, very hard to see this.
The brightness is very low there.
I should've taken a picture while I was lighting it up.
Would've been easier.
Okay, so let me pull out this.
Actually, I can't see it still.
So it would be...
Right...
Oh, actually, it's just in a circle.
That's easy.
Okay, nothing here.
Ah, wait, wait, wait.
I also want to try something here.
While I'm here.
Okay.
Sad face?
Is...
Oh, I never took a picture of, uh...
But that was that one.
That was that one.
No, that was...
Angry face?
I gotta go back and take a picture.
I think I have an idea here.
Basically, this is the idea.
I'm gonna take a picture of this up here.
I'm gonna switch the channel to...
I don't know, some kind of face.
And I'm gonna play the corresponding note.
And maybe something happens.
Maybe we have to do it multiple times.
Okay.
I need to see this again.
So we have angry face up here.
Angry face and...
Satisfied face.
Okay.
Wait, am I right?
Angry face, satisfied.
Okay.
Uh, let's do that.
Picture this one...
There.
We're gonna put this...
Uh, let's put it here.
Also, I'm just gonna write this...
With notes here, because I can't fucking see.
It's so dark.
One...
Two...
Actually, let's do it here.
Uh...
Let's draw the face, because I can't see through this.
Let's make red.
That's not red.
You lied to me.
There.
See that?
Then up here, we have this guy.
Who's angry.
Look at me!
Angry.
And then this guy...
Like that.
This is like stoic face.
This is angry...
Happy.
Actually, evil happy.
Someone who's up to no good, you know?
This is, uh...
I guess.
Okay.
Uh, that's good.
So...
We gotta switch the channel to here.
Now, I don't know if it's gonna be a sequence, or just, uh...
Something happens each time I do this.
Let's see.
Uh, let me zoom in on this a bit more.
There.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, I wanna go...
Actually, just try and play this here first since I'm here.
Okay.
Nothing?
I figured.
Like, obviously the TV is, uh, relevant.
Hold on.
I gotta blow my nose.
Okay.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good.
I fucked it up.
It's this one.
Angry?
No, that's, uh...
Which one is that?
That's the...
Top left.
So that is...
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Oh no!
I didn't mean to play it!
Oh, I think I fucked it up now.
Uh, I may have to restart.
Okay.
There.
How do I actually...
So, one thing I'm a little confused about.
When I bring out the flute, I can't activate, like, equip the flute without playing a note.
And I don't wanna accidentally play a note.
And if I hold the, uh, direction before I press the button, my character starts moving.
It's very janky.
Wait a minute.
So, we got that face.
Which is six...
One, two, three, four...
Oh, actually, I guess that doesn't matter.
It's more like, uh...
Top left.
And then...
That's the evil...
Oh, wait.
Oh, it's not actually in order.
Oh!
I understand!
I get it!
Check it out!
So, we're gonna do...
Um...
I forgot the order.
Start over!
Hold on.
Okay, angry?
That's this one.
One?
And then...
That one.
Which is...
Uh...
What is that?
It's the top left.
So, that's two.
Boom.
And...
Let me do it again.
That's the, uh, evil happy face.
I guess.
That's this one down here.
That's three.
That's the...
What?
Face.
That's when you ate too much.
It's this one.
Four.
And five.
Sad face.
Which is that one.
Five.
And then we have...
Neutral.
Unhappy face.
That's this one.
Six.
And super happy.
Super happy is...
That one.
Seven.
And then we're just missing one.
Eight.
Boom.
That's it!
You ready?
Here we go!
Uh...
Wait.
No, I need to see this while I do it, otherwise I can't do it.
So it would be, um...
It would be...
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Two.
A little something happened just now.
One.
Something jumped out.
Right here.
Like a little rabbit jumped out.
One.
Two.
It comes.
A little something happened just now.
Okay.
Bro, I didn't quite pay attention there to where that rabbit went.
Maybe it just pointed this out.
It did go to the right.
Okay, look at that.
We're soon at 1.
Maybe I should time this.
Hey, Google, set a timer for 18 minutes.
Alright.
We'll be ready for that.
Now, there's also some kind of thing going on up here.
Looks like the same sequence.
I want to try and play the same melody, but upstairs.
There we go.
Ah, but wait.
This is just the... This is just the mapping.
So how the hell do I get rid of these skulls?
And what's up with this fanny pack?
I'm sad I can't see the fanny pack on my character.
I bet it would look funny.
Beep-be-dee-boop.
Now, every time I see vines, I think there's a secret path.
Ah, shit.
Where do I go next?
That we already did.
I think I'm just gonna go back to HQ.
No.
Ah!
Love that sound.
Okay.
And then we want to go to, uh...
Well, the idea was to go up here, but we somehow did that already.
I didn't expect to come from the left side.
But we ended up doing it.
There's definitely areas where I can banish the ghosts to the nether realm.
But I forgot where those areas were.
I see a little something here.
That looks intriguing, doesn't it?
Like, look at that.
Right there.
Boop, boop, boop.
It's not a sea.
It's just a little half moon thing.
Uh, in order to get there...
Here, we are gonna go to...
Bear 3.
I think it's the best.
Bear 3 is 1, 2...
Where's my Bear 3?
It's up here.
Ah!
Didn't actually mean to fall all the way down.
Boom, baby!
Oh!
Uh...
I can't go this way.
That's right.
I gotta...
Dude!
Catch!
Am I even going the right way?
Kinda.
Except I can't get in there?
Also, did I just see...
No, never mind.
Swordfish!
Oh, yeah, that's...
Yeah!
Wait, haven't I been here?
How do I access that part?
I guess I have to come from here instead.
So, I walk down here and then down there.
Yeah.
Let me wait with this.
It's no doubt intriguing, but...
Wait, is he friendly now?
No, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Thought he was ignoring me there.
Down we go.
Like, I realize I already rolled credits on this game, but...
There's obviously more.
And I was...
I'm gonna play this game...
For the amount of time that I wanted to play this game today.
At least.
I'm just curious, you know?
What else I can find?
Especially, uh...
With all these weird slots everywhere.
I didn't mean to do that.
Well, you can put something circular in there, you know?
Or spherical.
Right, so...
We can actually just do this.
So convenient.
Wait, that...
Oh!
Right.
Can I beep you?
Okay, you don't like the beep.
What about this?
Stay away, foul creature!
No?
Okay.
Wow.
Uh...
Oh, fuck me!
Right, we found this.
Circular recess!
We put one shard in here, remember?
We gotta find more.
There's a giant, uh...
Wallaby?
From Australia.
How do I break that wall up there?
I'm losing my mind.
Bubbles!
Look at all these bubbles.
I need to find a place...
Where there's evil spirits in the ceiling.
And then I can ward them away with this light.
And something may happen.
Wait, key?
Do I have a key?
Only a house key.
Uh...
Wait, what?
I just took damage!
Please leave me alone.
Okay, so that path is, uh...
No...
No good.
It also looks like there may be something going on here, doesn't it?
Right there.
Like, if you really look at it, it looks like...
You can enter.
And to get down there...
I walk here.
Uh...
No, no...
Oh, shh!
God damn it.
It's fine.
See ya.
Wait a sec.
I may have seen something on the way there.
Look at that.
That right there, ladies and gentlemen, is a secret.
I guarantee it.
I'll prove it to you.
Oh!
Alright.
For some reason, I thought you were gone.
I can't find my fucking item.
Ugh.
Never mind.
I guess I'll...
Get the return trip.
Wait, where am I even going right now?
No!
Oh, my God.
Anyway, I saw evil spirits.
That's something.
Watch this.
Ready?
Oh, yeah!
No, wait.
There's a path.
Duh.
Fuck!
How on earth are you going to do this?
Oh.
Wait.
I think I fell down through that once.
You loop around, right?
Let's go, uh, fly back.
Oh, no.
And then what?
Now I'm here.
I'm actually close to this area.
Uh, next to where I couldn't enter.
I brought lights!
You're gonna stop throwing rocks at me?
Okay, you're not.
You are such assholes.
You like bubbles?
Here, have a lot.
There.
You like that, don't you?
Enjoy the bubbles.
No?
Okay.
They don't like the bubbles.
I kind of want to go back to, uh, the imprisoned T-Rexes.
Or whatever they're called.
They're not T-Rexes, but, you know.
The animals.
I also put a question mark here for some reason.
Was that a locked door?
It may have been.
And what about this, uh...
This place here, man.
My goodness.
That place.
Do I check that out again?
You know what else I could do?
I could just walk around through all the rooms and spam my...
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
So find chests.
You know?
May not be a bad idea.
Because I kind of want to find more.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I could technically walk down into those spirits now and press that button manually if I wanted to.
But I don't want to.
But I could.
I could do it.
In fact, I'm just going to look for, like, dark areas.
Because the map is super dense.
Any area that is, like, dark in between could be a potential spot, right?
For funsies.
Funsies, uh, businesses.
I don't want to...
Okay, that's fine.
No, why am I...
Why am I here?
Nothing.
I just want to teleport back.
Maybe in here.
Ah-ha!
Well, well, well.
Whoops.
How on earth am I going to get to that?
They're, like, a secret hidden entrance here.
Nope.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, maybe up here?
Fuck it!
Walrus, get out of my face.
Blocking my...
Okay.
I'm not seeing anything.
Like, how am I gonna...
...do that?
Can I break some of this somehow?
Wait, why didn't it show up?
Okay, look!
You gotta be in a specific spot to reveal the chest!
You can't do it from anywhere!
So, theory confirmed.
You can't just do it, like...
It doesn't work here, or...
Now it works.
Okay, I don't know why.
That one didn't work.
Didn't work.
Now it...
Okay, that's weird.
You gotta spam it a little bit.
Let's mark it.
Chest?
I don't honestly know how to get to that right now.
I could try and go...
F1...
Okay, maybe we work on the slots.
Because that one is a mystery.
Right?
I want to go back to the beginning.
Here.
So that is...
What's the best path?
Is it F2?
I wrote it down below, but does that mean...
I guess I can just check.
Oh, that's not F2.
That's B2.
F2 is this one down here, I think.
Yep.
Okay, it looks to me like we're missing two candles.
One in the center and one in the very bottom left.
So that means there's two candles to be found and two unlit candles somewhere, or I mean, two fire starters and two unlit candles somewhere in this world.
And you would think that those are located in areas of darkness.
So maybe that's worth another look, you know?
And this right here we opened.
That led to over there.
That was the whole snake deal, wasn't it?
I think so.
Yeah.
With the colored wall?
That was the snake place.
Oh, wait a minute.
Oh, this is the place where there's a door we can't open.
This one requires a key, I think.
Do we have a symbol for this?
Yeah.
Question mark is key.
Because that's the symbol that's above our heads when we try to get near there.
Okay, I'm not liking this place.
I will go back.
Or maybe I do explore up there a little bit.
Nah.
Take me back.
Now.
What other area is...
ripe for exploration?
This right here.
I put a skull here for some reason.
And there's a question mark.
There's all kinds of stuff happening here.
So let's head to this place.
And I also have a theory that we can reveal more arrows.
To free more of...
the animals.
With the light we have.
I don't know what the closest one is.
There's not a close one at all.
Or maybe...
No.
Not really.
Fuck.
Okay.
Bear one of this.
We gotta bear it.
Also, while we're here...
Okay.
Wake up!
Brian!
You gotta thoroughly check these areas.
Sometimes the chest will not reveal itself.
Or you do.
Ah, but to get there we need eggs, right?
That's the egg one.
Yeah.
Shit.
What was up here?
Right.
Oh!
Cuckoo!
Oh, no!
Wait, my timer isn't right.
Did my timer go off?
What happened to my timer?
My timer never activated.
What the hell, man?
I missed it.
Shit.
Ah, damn it.
I actually forgot about that.
Oh, it's right there.
Look at the chest.
There's probably something grand in there, huh?
Oh, wait a minute.
That is breakable!
Hey!
Oh.
Oh, okay.
What?
Probably a tutorial.
Because that's where we got this.
What about here?
Yeah, okay.
I'm not seeing anything there.
Jump down.
Now.
Will the light reveal secrets?
Save it.
Yep.
Not really.
Duck!
You like the bubbles?
Wait a sec.
Is that the same drawing?
It is.
Okay.
I thought something may have changed.
Actually, I'm being reminded of the candles here.
The candles were in a 4x4 grid, right?
I don't know if that's related or something.
Something about grits.
Yes!
Um... Yes, this is the way.
Oh!
Oh yeah, it's automatic!
I thought I was controlling it!
I was like, there's a weird delay here!
Ah!
Oh, it's gonna be this again, isn't it?
Okay, you know what?
Fuckin' do this.
Destroy it all.
Now...
I... Oh, I have to do this again, I think.
My nightmare.
Actually, I'm pretty good at this at this point.
And we gotta try all these items.
Any chests?
Hiding?
Whoop!
Whoa!
Nice.
Smooth.
Now we go here.
Ah.
Oh yeah.
Oops.
A little tricky.
Now, here's the secret.
Wait a minute, I have an idea.
Why can't I...?
Ah, okay, fine.
Fine!
Nothing breaks, huh?
Bro, this... this is impossible.
Unless I... fly with this?
Fuck.
Come on.
Go!
Oh my god, I'm so slow!
Okay, wait, let me... look.
Let's do it.
Now!
No, there's no way.
There's no way to do this.
Fuckin'...
Any chests?
Well, there's chests.
There we go!
I knew deep down in my gut that there's no way this was a skill check, you know?
There's just no way.
Maybe it is possible.
A moon egg!
Man, it's been a while since we found an egg, huh?
Jesus Christ.
Well, good shit!
We did it!
Finally!
Oh, it even... oh, this is so good.
It is immaculate!
There we go.
Now we can go back.
Because I'm a professional at this room now.
Notice how I just nailed everything.
First try.
Now, will the lantern work against these bastards?
What?
Maybe?
Was he invisible?
Yo, it works!
Yeah!
I love that!
Oh, that is fantastic news!
Oh, so nice!
Um...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's cute.
Wow, look at your head go.
His head disappeared.
And reappeared.
That's a...
Is that a chest I've already opened?
I can't tell.
I forgot, uh...
How an unopened chest looks...
Oh, yeah, I...
Yeah, I've definitely been up there.
Oi!
Fuck you!
I'm using this now.
Yeah, you can't hurt me.
Whoa!
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Oi!
Okay.
Wait, where am I going?
Why can't I...
There we go.
Oh, check it out.
Oh, I thought maybe it would reveal arrows over here.
Too bad.
I'm just happy I can traverse these regions now without the fear of these...
I don't even know.
Mice.
Rats.
Scabbards.
There's the question mark.
Let's go explore it.
Again.
I think it's best to just go up here.
Whoops.
Chest!
Chesterino!
It's up here.
But how do we get up there?
Oh, close.
Yeah!
But, uh...
Right.
Wait.
This doesn't help me.
I gotta come from above.
I see, I see.
Eat that.
It's always a gamble whether or not you wanna jump left or right when you're jumping off screen.
Oh, dude!
This is it?
Oh, no!
Uh, I gotta flick a switch.
Boom, baby.
Actually, let's just light up the region a little bit and let's see.
Okay.
Destructible!
What?
No?
Really?
I don't believe that.
Unless...
Why can't I flick this switch?
Ah!
Ah-ha-ha-ha!
There we go!
It's a dream egg.
Incredible.
Okay, you do you.
This one has been found.
Remove it.
Successful!
Next up!
Oh, wait!
This is part of the map now?
Why...
Why is this showing up on the map now?
Also, there's something in here.
There just has to be.
And maybe we enter from here.
So go all the way up and then right.
Wait, what is this?
Oh, this is where we got chased by the giant ass bitch.
I actually have a theory that there may be secrets down here.
Maybe with a bit of digging?
Yeah?
Or not?
Let's just have a bit of a look.
Okay.
Maybe not.
Oh, wait a minute.
I think I just realized...
When you eat the blue ones, that's when you get an...
Like an extra.
There's actually a difference in color on them.
That makes sense.
Makes a lot of sense.
Now, it looks like there's a path here, doesn't it?
I mean, we know...
Oh, is that the chest that showed up on the other side?
Maybe it is.
Do I dare remove that marker?
Ah!
I'm not sure.
Maybe it's not a good idea to remove that marker.
Let me see what's down here.
Show me the good times.
Chest on the right!
How are we gonna get there?
I guess we gotta go in there.
This seems pretty easy, actually.
So we go all the way down.
Let's just look for stuff on the way down.
Slinky!
Ho ho!
That's a long ass slinky.
Or a very long fall, I mean.
Look at that particle effect.
Isn't that wonderful?
So good.
Boink!
Okay.
I thought I could make the jump.
Uh...
Do I save the game?
I think I saved the game here.
Why is there just a little bit of water here?
That's...
suspicious, isn't it?
Or not?
Everything is suspicious now!
Suddenly I suspect everything.
Okay, now I wanna go up.
In fact...
What is this region again?
Let's, uh...
Check it out.
Oh, you...
You bastard!
Alright, but I know how to deal with you.
The question is...
How do I do that while doing the bubble?
Well, maybe I don't care about you, actually.
Yeah, this is fine.
That's cool.
I have my eyes on a chest here.
And I'm gonna get it.
Thank you.
Now...
Right up.
Boink!
Oh, shit.
This is gonna be tough.
We gotta do it this way.
What just happened there?
I didn't mean to do that!
Frick!
I think we're okay.
Except this is not the way...
Dammit.
Also, for some reason...
Oh, man!
That lantern is really nice for lighting up places, too.
Not just in the immediate vicinity, but just in general.
So good.
Right, so here...
We wanna go...
Up, left.
That seems about right.
Is that Brohan?
And here we are.
This should...
This should be the area.
Oh, wait!
How have I never seen this?
Hello?
He's right there!
Oh, my God, really?
What?!
The range!
Okay, that's clearly not working.
Oh, he likes the music!
Thanks, bro!
I found a key!
Outplayed, outfooled.
What do you think of my light?
Okay, okay, okay, fine, fine.
They're w-w-w-w-w-wapping on me.
Not sure how to feel about that.
There, go.
Wow, that bounced off.
So...
I see the path.
Pool.
Can't reach me now, can ya?
Hehehe.
Yoink!
A match!
Fan...
Fantastic.
There's stuff up there?
No.
Okay!
Nice, nice, nice.
Now, we were in a dark place just before.
I can imagine there being, like, a candle there, you know?
Because it's a dark place.
So I'm gonna take one last look down here.
How do I get down?
Oh, here.
Yeah, check out how dark that is.
Except I'm not seeing a candle.
I'm blind to it.
Yeah, notice how the chest is only revealed if the particles are hitting it.
You see that?
The particles right now do not hit it from this angle with the reflections.
There.
There it got hit.
So...
I can't just trust activating that in any room, and if there's nothing there, then I'm like, yeah, it's clean.
That's not how that works.
There's this place.
Oh yeah, levers.
I could go on a shark trip.
Which takes me all the way up here.
Maybe not.
I'm gonna take a break.
Uh...
Oh!
Stop timer!
Maybe that's what it is here.
Look!
13 hours, 20 minutes.
12,135 steps.
That's a lot of steps.
So if I walk a little bit...
Yeah, cool.
Yeah, let's take a quick break.
I'll see you guys in five minutes.
Jackie has something to say.
I don't know if you can hear her.
She's purring.
Jackie.
Wanna go down?
Jackie was hanging out.
As soon as I left my chair, of course she jumps up because it's nice and hot now that I've been sitting here.
So I didn't have the heart to just take her away, so...
I put her on my lap and then now she left.
There it is.
Okay, back to it.
What the...
Goddamn loose connection on the cable.
Every time I...
Reorient myself here or sit down.
It all messes up.
Okay, there we go.
Right, I was in here.
Uh...
I don't see anything special here.
I wish there was an easier way to...
Hold on, if I'm on keyboard...
Maybe there's like a keybind you can use for each...
Six, four, three...
No, I don't think so.
Because I absolutely hate having to scroll through these items and actually...
Ugh!
Wish I could press one or two or three and just have...
That...
Item pop up, you know what I mean?
Ah, this is not it.
This way.
Uh...
This is very dark.
There was one spot where there were...
Ghosts in the ceiling.
I wanna get back to there.
Also, since I'm here...
Okay.
Alright, in this spot, I wanna check for arrows.
Yeah, let's go up here, actually.
What do I see?
Actually, I see some HP.
Nice.
I don't wanna jump in the shark's mouth.
Or do I?
Nah.
Nope.
Take me back up here, now that we have some lights.
Look how much that lights up!
That is incredible!
Okay, so we should be walking around with this in this region.
Just in case something...
Lights up, you know?
Let's go for a ride.
Why do I think there's something in this...
Box right there in the center of the screen?
It's all dark.
Wait, what was that?
What was that?
Oh, okay, never mind.
Whoa!
Close one.
Uh...
Nope.
Not seeing any arrows at all, even with the light.
Yeah, nothing.
Maybe on the way down.
Ah, shit!
Really?
I thought I timed it correctly.
Now.
Good.
Good, good, good.
So, we can definitely destroy this.
And then this lights up, right?
Whoops, I didn't need to do that.
Okay, there's another light...
Yeah, it does light up a little bit.
Not too much.
I think we can pretty much write this place off.
With the exception of, perhaps, this little area here.
Uh, there.
I don't know how we would enter there, but...
Could be something.
I'm gonna make a circle.
Ah, maybe just an arrow.
That's a horrible arrow.
There we go.
Okay, so...
There's also stuff here.
I put two arrows on the right.
Maybe breakable wall.
Take me down.
In fact, wait a minute.
This looks...
Oh!
Look at that!
Fuck me, dude.
It was right there in front of my fa...
Hello.
Uh-oh.
Um...
Right.
You are definitely not friendly.
You gonna come back?
I don't think so.
Can I stand on that cage in the center?
Or is it ogre?
Chests, chests, chests...
I don't see any.
Except the one in the center, of course.
Yep!
Okay, we can stand on it.
Nice.
What an ugly piece of shit you are.
Break it!
Ooh!
Would you look at that!
Oh, hold the phone!
We've been there!
Oh, we looped around!
We're on the left side now.
Oh, that's...
That's death, isn't it?
I wanna go back to that guy and he's gonna...
Fuck me up!
You know it, I know it.
Every...
One knows it.
Shit.
I see something on the bottom left.
Bottom left is a for-sure-something's-going-on-there situation.
We're gonna wait for this guy...
Actually, maybe, uh...
Maybe that will work.
He doesn't care at all.
How do I...
Do this?
I know how to do this.
It's gonna be a little tricky...
Boy, that's close!
D'oh!
We made it!
Wait, what?
Oh no, we didn't!
I thought I was in the hole!
Fuck!
Um...
That's it!
Destroy these goddamn thingies.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, that's it.
Can't quite reach.
Ooh, it's close!
Yeah, come on!
No way!
Uh...
Hmm...
It's the last one there that's gonna be a problem!
So how are we gonna swing that?
One HP as well.
This is not good.
Maybe I can, from the other side, throw the disc.
But I would have to be at the correct elevation.
Maybe it actually works.
No, I can't stand there either.
Fuck!
Okay, I have an idea.
This is gonna require some dexterity, okay?
Uh...
Let me see.
So, one, two...
Oh, it's just one!
It's just one!
Nice!
So, one, one...
We're gonna be quick here.
Go!
Fuck all y'all!
There it is!
Look at that.
Beautiful.
Now we wait.
Go!
Maybe too early!
No!
You had it!
Fuck!
Where are we even?
Ugh...
I don't know where I am now.
God damn it.
Where the hell was I?
Uh...
Right.
Okay, so...
We gotta go...
To the right.
Shit balls, man!
I had that!
Ugh, not these birds.
Tell me there's a different way.
Ugh...
Pain.
Dude...
Traversing this map, just to go to A to B, may be the worst part about this game.
Like, just let me get there, you know?
Like, I don't wanna do this a million times.
Um...
This way.
No.
Oh, God.
Is it...
Here?
Good enough.
Now what?
Now we just go straight.
Okay, okay.
Good.
I was on the right path.
Save the damn game!
And then...
Up here...
Oh, we don't need to break the floor again, do we?
Nope.
Still broken.
Okay, okay.
Here we go, here we go.
Nice.
Be quick now.
Oh!
There's spikes on the left!
I thought it was like, just...
I don't...
I don't know what I thought that was.
But those are spikes!
Fuck me!
Okay, well in that case...
Then I know what to do.
One...
Okay, I can do...
One to the right.
Okay.
Yeah!
Oh my God!
We made it!
There's a spike right on top of me!
Oh my God!
That is frickin' terrifying!
What?!
Huh?
Okay.
I don't know what the fuck just happened there.
Why did I...
This is what I mean.
Like, when you don't see what's off screen...
It's a crapshoot!
Like, you gotta guess which side you gotta be on!
It's weird.
Uh...
We're in trouble!
Trouble!
Blast!
Blast mode!
Blast it!
Oh!
Okay.
So now...
Left side.
Slowly...
I see!
Well...
Shit.
That's how I...
Get here.
From up top.
But, but, but...
This chest is gonna be the goddamn end of me.
I have no idea...
How to get that chest.
Like, zero idea.
Not even an inkling of an idea.
Huh.
There's also something right above me.
Over here.
Like, what's that?
Ah, wait.
That's just gonna loop around, isn't it?
Just gonna loop around.
Uh...
Well, fuck.
Oh, well.
I mean, we did discover some new stuff there.
That's something.
And I can remove some...
Items over here now.
So, this one...
It's gone.
This one's gone.
Nah...
You know what?
There's probably nothing there.
This, however, looks hella suspicious, doesn't it?
Right down here?
Like, what's that all about?
That's a big ol' hole here.
But then again, where does it lead to?
There's nothing here.
There's no room for anything to be there.
This right here.
There's something there.
And maybe also here.
And here.
Let's go to Bear 2.
I have a good feeling about Bear 2.
So, let's get to...
In fact, I may see an entrance.
So, we gotta go down over here.
Also, I should be using this everywhere.
Oh, right.
So, last time we were here, we came from the left.
There's this lovely area.
And what a lovely area it is, actually.
Is there something on the right?
No response.
And we go left.
Ah, it does kinda look like...
There's something right here.
And access to this place.
Maybe.
That's a big maybe.
Whoops, I didn't mean to fall all the way down.
Damn it!
Oh, but wait a sec.
Whoa!
That's new!
He's gonna...
Reset.
Basically, the idea now...
Watch this.
I know how to...
So, if we do it there...
It's gonna stop.
This guy's gonna go back.
So, yeah, now...
The bottom one keeps going.
We gotta time this now.
Wait.
I may have fucked up the timing.
Maybe like this?
Yeah!
Haha!
Oh, shit.
No, you're supposed to fall off!
Sir!
Follow my light...
Thingy.
There we go!
But now I have to make him walk right.
How I do that?
Man, this is a conundrum?
Oh, wait, wait!
We scare him!
Scare him!
Yeah!
There it is!
Oh.
This has to be a candle.
I don't trust...
Future Egg!
What's that sound?
Oh, okay.
It's Jaggy scratching at her scratching post.
For some reason it was very bassy.
Not sure what was going on there.
Okay, that was nice.
Found a little secret there.
I mean, look at all this empty space here.
Surely...
There's going to be stuff there.
No?
This is the entrance to it.
Or maybe even...
Here.
Yeah.
For sure.
Okay, so...
We did that.
Go back.
What do we do now?
Okay, that was good, that was good.
Let's check out the little circle I made.
So this way.
Oh, thanks Brian.
Candle is lit.
I'm looking for arrows.
This could be a place with arrows.
It just has that vibe, you know?
The arrow vibes.
Yeah.
Damn it.
What am I doing?
Keep the lights on.
Any arrows hiding in the wall plaster?
What's that?
Oh, nice.
Blue fruit.
Also called a boot.
So...
I mean, right now it looks blue, but it's not.
It's actually red.
You can get fooled here.
Oh, this spot.
I remember this.
So right above me it seems, huh?
Something's going on up there.
Nothing up there.
I guess I can try to come in from the top or left.
But that looks like dice to me.
Dicey situation.
What do we have there?
Beepity boop.
Oh!
That's the chest we saw from before.
Yeah, these are dice.
Like, there's gotta be something in this pyramid.
Perhaps not.
I don't know where to go.
Maybe up top and try to go down from there?
So let's go back to bear two.
That's actually faster.
And then from here...
We go...
Actually, we go this way.
And then straight down.
It doesn't look like there's a path, does it?
Unless it's destructible.
Nope.
That's not gonna do anything for me.
Not that way.
I guess I'm just kind of assuming that there's something in there.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Maybe here.
That's still a bear too though.
Now check three out of four directions.
Let's check the last direction!
I mean, uh...
One of them's gotta be right.
Or not.
Oh shit, how do I get...
Over there?
I guess I go right instead.
Yeah.
Here.
Down.
And then this way.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This place was super mysterious.
There's definitely something up there!
The way we did this last time...
Uh, we had the guy drop down, hit the button.
Yep.
Come here!
Maybe I have to go over here.
Yeah, that's it.
So I gotta get up there.
That opens...
The chest on his head, right.
So I think I gotta leave a slinky here.
Keep that open.
Then we lead this guy over here.
Yeah!
There's a chest up there!
I saw it!
Alright.
Uh, sir, would you like to come over here?
Perhaps.
Also, I gotta be quick.
Oh, you don't want... okay.
Fine.
Uh...
Oh, but now I can...
No!
Brian!
Brian, please!
Quick!
Ah!
Okay, now.
Oh, he was close!
Yes!
Ha ha!
A zen egg.
Oh!
Oh, okay.
What is this now?
Oh ho ho!
Would you look at that.
Ooh!
That's how I'm gonna get the chest!
I gotta walk on one of these!
I'm talking about the other place I was in.
Walk, noble steed!
Let's go!
Wonderful!
Thanks, Brian!
You are the man.
It's a universal basic egg.
That's incredible.
U-B-E.
Is that how, uh, the people get paid here?
In this...
In this world.
Oh!
There's definitely something up there.
Maybe not.
Okay, I was fooled.
Aha!
Now we're on the other side of that.
Beautiful.
How right was I about this circle, huh?
Hehe.
We're finding eggs.
We're totally egging right now.
I love to egg.
But how do I get...
Oh, right.
This way.
Good, good, good.
So we can leave here.
Next up, let's try and find out how to get inside that other circle I made.
I think it may be from...
Over here.
Oh, of course it is!
Look up there!
It's easy!
It's so obvious, too.
How on earth did I miss that?
I must have been blind last time I was here.
Or maybe I didn't have the tools.
To actually make my...
There.
But can't I just...
No.
Oh, you mad now?
Stay mad, bro.
I'm gonna light you...
Blinded!
No?
Uh...
So we gotta make him...
Walk on those.
Oh, you bastard.
Okay.
You're not gonna let me do that?
That's fine.
What if I do it all the way over here?
Aw, you're fast, eh?
Okay.
Fine.
Like...
This walking dude is never gonna reach this.
Am I crazy?
Maybe we scare it off of it?
Yeah!
But...
Maybe there's a...
But we gotta scare him off of it every time.
Oh!
I get it.
I understand.
The problem is, I have no more firecrackers, so...
What then?
Then I'm...
Then I can't do anything.
Eh?
Give me light.
Really?
Do we have any here?
Nothing here.
Dude, there's no way I need that, right?
Maybe I can...
Scare it off in some other way?
Oh, actually, there's HP.
I want that.
Come here, Brian.
Eh.
Thanks.
Oh, wait, I'm full HP.
Never mind.
I also theorized there's something below here.
Maybe I'll check that out real quick.
And before I forget, let's just...
Yeah, okay.
I have circles there already.
Where's my character?
Oh.
This looks like...
There's something going on in there.
No?
Brian, are you strong?
Can you break down this wall for me?
Hey?
Oh!
Cuckoo!
I'm not there, though.
Bro.
I think something happens if you're there when the cuckoo happens.
Do I...
Really have to go find more of this?
There's no way.
Like, I don't...
I don't even see any in the vicinity.
Try going up.
Oh, Brian, thanks for saving me.
You're the realist.
You're so real, you're in a state.
That makes no sense.
Crack my fires!
Fire my crack.
Uh...
Go upstairs.
Ah, save the game, I guess.
No reason not to.
Bro, give...
Give me a firecracker.
Hello?
Where are the firecrackers at?
Here's why I think I may not need a firecracker.
They would put more firecrackers nearby.
That would be good game design.
And they didn't do that, so...
Wait, what's this place?
Oh, yeah.
This fucking guy.
So, obviously we can do something here, but I'm not sure what.
Theory time.
I think this guy is sitting on an egg.
And...
If we scare him off of that, somehow he will reveal the egg to us.
There's literally no firecrackers anywhere.
Well...
Guess I'm not doing that.
Oh shit.
Fuck!
Well...
Only way out.
Take me home.
Country road.
Bear 2.
Let's go left.
I also want to find that room with all the...
This is the room.
Look how I disperse.
But can I get up there?
While equipping the lantern is the question though.
Dammit.
It goes very...
I guess I could make a...
Bubble here.
Oh, that's so sneaky though!
Firecracker spotted!
Heck yeah!
Thanks.
Another one...
Oh, this is it.
Firecracker country.
More HP.
So what is...
Oh yeah, this was the place.
Maybe you find another firecracker.
Just in case, you know?
Telephone.
Wait a minute.
This looks weird.
Also this right here.
Look at that!
Wait
a goddamn second.
Show me the chest.
It's somewhere upstairs from here.
Anymore firecrackers?
Just uno mas.
Uno mas.
Don't even take the chance.
How about I can't even proceed here?
Okay.
I...
Don't know.
Back to bear two.
We got some firecrackers.
We can try this again.
I know how to do it.
At least with a firecracker I know how to do it.
I just gotta...
Do it right.
And the room in question is...
This way.
I believe.
Save.
Now that we have the firecrackerinos.
Right.
Okay.
Let's go.
There we go.
Okay.
So here's the...
Here's the deal.
We're gonna throw a firecracker.
He's gonna fall off to the next.
So we actually gotta flip this immediately.
And then when he's on that side, we go...
Here.
And when he's there, we go here.
He's gonna go all the way...
There, then there.
Yeah.
Okay.
I see.
Nice.
Yes.
Boom.
Wait a minute.
Oh.
Ha ha ha.
I'm a genius.
A value egg.
Is there a little turd on top of that egg?
Or what is that?
Maybe a cowboy hat.
Alright.
Nailed it.
Remove that.
Add it to my egg collection.
46 eggs.
And we have a key and a match.
I am furiously looking for, uh...
Candles to light.
This looks suspicious.
No, no, no.
Okay.
Maybe not.
Alright.
Moving on.
Let's try and get here now.
So...
Straight down and left.
Ah, we can't go straight down.
Yes, we kinda can.
Over here.
Left, left, left, left.
Oh, nice.
Firecracker.
Yeah, for sure.
Dude, it's so satisfying finding secrets in this game.
Oh, that's so good!
Mmm.
Look at all my HP.
Razzle-dazzle egg.
With lasers in their shoes.
Remove this.
Oh!
That feels good.
Next!
Fuck it.
Secret thousand...
Finder...
498...
2094.
Uh, here now.
That's the next destination, baby.
Now, where do we have potential access points?
Here!
Here.
This is it right there.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, baby.
Alright, let's calm down.
It's in there.
The best way is to go to... which bear?
Which bear is it?
I know it's a bear.
We're totally bearing on this one.
Bear one.
Love bear one.
It's my first bear.
Wake up!
I mean, sorry for interrupting your sleep.
But, you know.
Gotta be done.
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, never mind.
Okay.
Now we want to go... straight to the right, actually.
That should be an easy one here.
Whoa.
Almost fell down.
Crackers!
Wait, I can hold six crackers now?
Oh, that's what the fanny pack does!
100%-o, friendo.
That's what's happening.
The fanny pack.
Whoa!
Uh-huh.
Huh?
Oh!
Oh my god, what?
Really?
Okay, dude.
Uh... We got ourselves a puzzle.
This is obviously... a cat.
Where else have we seen a cat?
Dude, I can change every pixel.
Oh!
Whoa!
It was a piece of rock that fell.
Maybe I... Wait, have we seen any... anything like this anywhere?
Maybe we have to draw this.
I don't know.
What the hell, man?
That's crazy.
Also, what happened?
I... I...
Wait, the... Wait, what?
Oh!
Oh, okay.
It's the receiver up there.
I guess I blew something up remotely.
Well, we gotta find an image somewhere that we can kinda replicate, I guess.
That's the only way.
Because I don't know what to change these to, right?
We could try and get rid of everything except, uh, the cat.
Complete shot in the dark here, but...
There's no way we have to empty the entire board, right?
That's weird, man.
I... I don't... I don't know.
I don't... What is... What are we doing here, you know?
Alright.
Let's find an entrance here.
Alright, that doesn't work.
I feel like this has to be the entrance over here somehow.
That makes sense to me.
Like, how is that not... This looks destructible.
Doesn't it?
Look at the floor!
Right here!
I feel scammed.
Fine, I'm not gonna force it.
Let's head down a little.
We're gonna try every angle on this bitch.
I'm telling you.
Nothing's gonna evade us.
Is that gonna lead me back up?
Kinda.
If I go by here?
Eh, that's not gonna work.
Uh... Hmm... Back... Down... If we go down... Like, there's no way that's an empty space.
I just refuse to believe it.
I did put a marker for a chest there.
Let's go check it out.
Oh wait, didn't I already... Didn't I already get this one?
I'm pretty sure I got this one.
Did I just forget to remove the mark?
I'm just gonna double check.
Five out of six!
Yeah, I... I just forgot to remove it.
Okie dokie-ly!
Okay, uh...
I see a potential for...
Here?
Maybe here.
And I'm pretty far off right now.
Let's hit...
This way.
Cause you can't tell me there's nothing in there.
I just, uh... I won't believe it.
Even if Billy Basso himself appeared from the shadows and said, Nooo, Oliver!
Nothing in there!
I wouldn't trust him.
You know why?
Cause he's a puzzle game maker!
Wait, shit.
Ah!
Oh wait, I can just walk up here.
We're fine, we're fine.
Now this one...
We cannot bubble that one!
Fuck.
How do we do?
How the hell?
Do I have to go all the way around the left side?
Oh no.
I think so.
That's fine.
Oh yeah!
You!
That's an empty chest.
Maybe I can lure him out with a certain melody.
Let me try every tone.
That would be a fun puzzle.
If you play the right tone as the first one, he comes out slightly.
And then if you play the next tone wrong, he goes back in.
But if you do it right, he comes out a little more, a little more, a little more, until he's all the way out.
You know?
And then you have the melody.
Wouldn't that be cool?
Wow, look at all my HP!
I have so much!
Oh, wait!
That looks breakable!
Look at the floor!
I mean, floor slash...
roof there.
You can't do it from...
There's definitely something up there.
That's confirmed now.
Dang.
Stop pushing the...
thingy.
Losing my mind.
How do I get up there?
Hello?
Oh!
Made it.
What?
No way.
This is what I mean.
Like...
This cannot be a dead end.
Okay, so it's gotta be...
from up there, top, right?
So how the hell?
This way.
Also, I gotta blow my nose.
Back up this way.
It's quite the detour, huh?
I was kind of expecting this to go back to default.
What if you forget what the default setting was here?
Are you just fucked, or...?
I mean, I took a picture of it, so I'm fine, but...
Just saying.
Even this place makes me mysteriously...
suspicious.
Uh...
This could be it.
Oh...
It's just a dark map.
We've been here.
But, have we destroyed things?
Ha-ha!
Very good.
Oh, crap.
Oy!
Almost got me.
Oh, okay.
Oh, and now it shows up on the map.
Okay.
Well, that's...
Man, I was kind of hoping it would be a new place, you know?
Well, that's cool.
It looks like there's stuff underneath it.
Wow, look at this.
Notice how the map is almost perfectly rectangular?
There is 100% stuff all the way here.
I can guarantee it.
There's something here, there's something here.
It's an eggplant.
Or a...
Something.
And here.
Right?
Like, look how dense this map is.
Wow.
We can remove this.
And that.
But...
I still feel like there's something here.
The bad news is, even though I unlock what looks to be a shortcut here, it's not really a shortcut, because I can't get back up.
Uh, it's not possible.
No.
Not possible.
What is the next destination, then?
I guess down here.
A color wall there, too.
Maybe we go to the eggplant.
Do I see an axis anywhere?
Axis...
It is not apparent at all from the map where the axis could be.
Maybe here?
Potentially here?
It's not...
It's not clear.
I can also go back down here and try out things now that I have light and all that.
Right, there's this place, too.
What is that?
Oh, yeah.
That was my home.
Color wall.
This is the...
Bubble Kingdom.
F1.
Let's go to F1.
Uh, that's this one.
Bubble Kingdom.
Oh, that's so useful now, actually, having this.
But do I go down there?
Wait a sec.
That would lead to the right side of the map over there, I guess.
I wanna go up.
So that's here.
Yes.
I don't mind checking out the top again here.
Let's just...
Ascend.
Ascend with Gorb.
The man himself.
Ah!
I messed it up.
How am I so bad at this now?
What am I seeing?
I see potential.
Breakable floors?
I'm not seeing any.
Ah, crap.
I guess there's a better way to do this.
Okay, so here...
Oh wait, that looks...
That looks like a...
Spot, doesn't it?
Yep.
I think I've been in there, actually.
Give it another look, maybe?
Oh, was it a button?
I think it was.
Looks like I reached the maximum amount of HP you can have in the game.
That chest is empty.
Crap.
Okay.
So from here...
There's a potential entrance up...
Near the ceiling.
Oh...
Let's not accidentally fall into this guy.
Oh yeah, they even have stuff up there to prevent...
Something's going on here.
I can feel it in my bones.
Break this shit.
In fact, uh...
I wanna...
Stand on you!
I can't?
Wow.
Save the game?
Yeah, suck it in.
It's gonna be so annoying.
Okay, that actually doesn't look like an entrance.
Maybe I'm wrong.
Yeah, it doesn't look like it.
Oh!
But I see something up there!
That could be it.
Oh no!
Mistakes.
Yep!
Oh wait, we've been here.
Ah shit.
Like, it looks like there's an entrance there.
But here...
Oh, I didn't mean to drop down.
Let's go this way again.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Oh my god, look at this room.
This way.
Ah, the bubble columns.
I think I'm definitely...
Oh, see!
What was that?
Oh yeah, we also have this room.
Oh, we did this already.
Okay.
Oh!
Wait.
How...
How am I supposed to...
Oh god!
Oh shit!
I forgot about this!
Oh no!
Oh wait, there's no entrance up there at all.
That...
That's not an entrance.
Could be here.
Like a little...
Like that, you know?
That...
I mean, I saw a little something here.
Like there's a little pipe there, but it's so hard to get to with the fucking guy eating my bubbles.
Uh...
Wait, I didn't actually mark the guy.
Did I ever go on that?
Hold on.
We have a new plan.
I wanna see where that leads me.
That may even lead me in there.
Back we go.
Oh shit.
Made it.
Except...
You can't actually go back.
Oh yeah, you can.
Uh, sir, where are you taking me?
Oh,
there we go!
Fuck yeah!
Alright!
Uh...
What?
No, no, no.
Back up.
Stop eating my bubbles.
Okay.
How much you wanna bet it's not this one?
Ah!
I didn't mean to jump into it, actually.
Oh, never mind.
I think we're on the right track.
One.
Oh!
There's a button in the top left!
I missed it.
Whoops.
But that's maybe okay.
Suck me in!
Thank you.
Okay, so if you eat a blue one when you don't have full red, it's just gonna be a red.
Wait...
Hmm...
I have a feeling.
I'm gonna...
Okay, fine.
Jump in!
Okay.
Ah!
Oh my god.
Asshole!
Stop eating my bubbles!
Dup!
There we go.
Take me on a trip.
Ha-ha!
Wait a minute.
There could be a secret up here.
For sure.
There's also this spot here.
Look!
All this...
Three out of three!
So we go back?
How do we go back?
Oh, right.
Uh...
Let me try the top one.
Made it.
Suck the bubble!
Oh, okay.
But...
What about...
There's a dog right above there.
Uh-oh.
Whoa!
Let's not forget the chest as well.
Let's mark it, actually.
Uh...
Where was it?
Somewhere here.
Friendship egg.
Cool.
I like that.
Save.
Take me back.
Suck it!
Magic egg.
Dude, we are just collecting the eggs right now.
How many do we have?
49.
Not bad at all.
Um...
I do feel like I want to go back up to the dark area here.
Because...
Reasons.
Wait, I want to get to here, right?
And maybe there's a way to do it.
So...
Asshole.
Oh my...
These guys are such assholes.
Oh right, I'm here now.
That's not what I want.
Or is it?
By the way, I should mark this.
So...
Uh...
Wait.
Here?
Takes me to...
There.
I think?
You take me...
Here.
No!
Ah...
Fuckin' hell.
These sharks are so annoying!
It's insane!
They're so annoying!
Okay, so...
Which one?
Come on!
Is it you?
It is you!
Just spam the bubbles!
There we go!
We're back!
Gotta be some way to get over there.
Too dark to see the map.
Now I'm starting to think...
Maybe this is an entrance there.
Or...
Ah!
This one perhaps?
No, that's gonna lead to the other side of the map.
Uh...
It could just be a shark from down here.
Another one I haven't tried yet.
Oh, let's remove this as well.
So what now?
Let's go again.
I think I've tried all the sharks.
That one...
We've tried that one and that one.
I don't wanna accidentally fall in.
This one's just gonna take me down, isn't it?
This is a mess.
There.
That's a connection...
Oh, man.
That is a mystery.
You know what, actually?
I have a theory.
Check this out.
It's probably connected here, right?
So if I can access via here...
Meaning...
From the right side of the map...
Here.
Somehow.
Maybe even...
There.
That even looks like an...
Like an entrance.
Doesn't it?
That would be a...
Great puzzle to get there, you know?
Use the...
Repeating nature of the map.
Also, these two...
Oh, we did that already?
That we did already?
R?
Why did I put an R there?
I'm not sure.
It was one of the animals.
Oh, this one.
Right.
Reptile, I think.
Now, this area...
Is also interesting.
That's a bean.
I drew a bean.
And here, too.
Perhaps the way to get to here...
Is either via this...
Endpoint.
Which I doubt.
Or...
Somehow access via...
Oh, yeah.
Here, maybe.
That even looks like an entrance.
Doesn't it?
Bear, too.
It's always bear, too.
Straight to the right.
Oh, but it's gonna be a pain, isn't it?
This is the pain area.
Yeah.
It's full of pain.
Here.
That takes me there.
And then the top part...
Oh, okay.
No, no.
I'm wrong, then.
It should be higher up.
So, somewhere here.
Which is...
Wait, that doesn't make any sense.
The scale here does not correspond.
Like, look at the X...
You see that this is across and moving around?
Look at the horizontal line here.
I'm gonna keep it straight, okay?
Right here.
That doesn't fit at all!
The scale is off.
Maybe I'm miscounting it.
Wait, now I'm down...
What?!
It should be right below me here.
Nothing, eh?
Well, now I'm really confused.
Look at this weird stone here.
It's green.
Or...
Maybe it's metal or something, but...
Something's up with that.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
I can't go that way now.
Huh.
Bro, I don't know.
We got a key though!
Maybe we go home and try it.
We know there's a door there, right?
That could be an idea.
And the best way home...
Is...
Actually via the...
Elevator here.
So...
Or is it?
Is it?
There's a better way?
This is a hell of a way though.
F...
No.
Bare one.
Okay.
Let me go here.
Also, how long...
How many do I need?
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Thirty, six...
Oh god, I miscounted.
One, two...
So...
Yeah.
I think it's like 64-ish.
It would make sense.
Okay, so now I wanna go...
Oh, actually I have to go up here.
There's a Paraguay in the way.
Can't have that.
Oh!
Look at that!
Spot it!
Watch this.
Ultimate...
Never mind, don't watch that.
That's...
That's embarrassing.
We're doing it the old way.
Boom!
A holiday egg.
Cool.
Holiday...
Eggs...
Are the best.
Dude, tomorrow is, uh...
Halloween, right?
No wait, that's...
Today's the 29th.
Dude, I'm actually kind of excited for Ark Raiders.
That's coming out tomorrow.
Like, I saw a, uh...
Gameplay trailer of it.
And I've never played an extraction shooter before.
I played like, what?
Maybe like...
A couple hours of Tarkov.
Back when it came out many, many years ago.
And I didn't like it at all.
So, you know, I'm a little biased against extraction shooters, but...
This actually looks pretty cool.
I like the aesthetic of it and all that.
What was I doing?
I went too far up.
I was on autopilot while I was talking.
I need to go...
Oh yeah!
There could be...
This guy is also...
Rotating.
Look at you rotating.
Nice.
Except...
Do I wanna go...
I forgot what this did.
Oh!
Right.
That's what I need.
There we go.
We're going home.
We're homeward bound.
Actually, while we do this...
I'm just gonna do that at times.
Homeward bound.
Homeward boner.
Is what man versus game used to say.
When you played Dark Souls 1.
Now you cannot stop me from going home!
Bastard.
And there's also this...
Weirdness.
Like...
What is even going on here, you know?
That is just...
Absurd.
Oh!
We're almost at a cuckoo!
We're gonna stay home until the cuckoo hits.
Where are you gonna be when the cuckoo hits?
You know?
No!
I can't unlock it!
I got a key though!
What do you mean?
Wait...
Look at that poster on the wall!
Green, yellow, blue...
How many colors did I have in the...
The cat...
Board.
How many colors did I have?
Was it four?
Four colors?
One, two, three, four...
No, there's way too many colors there.
Well, what are we gonna do now while we wait?
Maybe I'll just take another look around this place.
Why am I able to, uh...
Or why is there like a bridge here?
That almost means I can go below, no?
And then jump up again.
Okay, this right here!
There's a chest right there!
Uh...
Did I try the combination here?
I forgot already if I did.
Let me just try it while we wait.
Okay, let me bring this up.
Uh...
Here.
Okay.
I'm just gonna do it while this is open.
It's easier for me.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six...
Seven...
Eight...
No.
Okay.
What about...
Uh...
Well, I don't know then.
What about in here?
Light it up a bit?
Dude, where the hell are the arrows?
There's gotta be arrows somewhere.
I wanna rescue more...
Uh...
Thingies.
God, I...
Oh, wait a minute.
Maybe it's...
Another explosion?
Remote controlled?
From a specific spot?
What?
Okay, let me think about this.
So...
There's a bunch of skulls.
And...
Actually, all the skulls have different rotations.
Some of them are pointing straight at the screen, some are pointing left and right.
You see that?
Uh...
Why is there a malformed bird?
Okay, they were just stacked.
Never mind.
Let me go check.
We're almost there.
Zero, zero, zero on all three.
Maybe we gotta be here when it happens?
Isn't it kinda brutal that this is real-time?
This is a real-time clock.
Like, what's up with that?
Also...
What is this stuff in the center?
There's circles?
Bubbles?
I don't know.
I'm just gonna wait, guys.
For that clock to hit, uh...
Full hour.
What else is there in here?
Maybe I missed more.
I guess we'll...
Double check everything.
Oh!
Oh yeah!
Right.
That was a thing.
What if I hit the bubbles with the bubbles?
What if I need to, like, blow a bubble here?
Here?
Here, here, here?
And then have them all align at the same time something happens.
Imagine.
That'd be one...
Two, three...
That's impossible.
You can't do that.
There's no way to do that fast enough.
No.
I mean, unless...
You just spam the shit out of it.
I don't know what I'm trying to do.
But, like, look at this, uh...
On the wall there.
That almost looks like some kind of...
Well...
Some kind of computer speak.
You know what I mean?
You know how computers, they're like ones and zeros, right?
You could almost...
I don't know.
Maybe there's something there.
Like, that is a very peculiar poster.
Five, two.
Better than, uh...
Six, seven.
Am I right?
I gotta be honest, I don't even know what six, seven means.
But I see it in the Danish news.
There was a news article.
Apparently it's a meme or something.
But apparently young kids in Denmark are going around saying six, seven.
And...
I don't understand what it means.
I feel like an old man.
That's like, what is all this?
You know, like, I don't get it.
What does it mean?
I don't get it.
But it's apparently a thing.
Okay.
Are you ready for something crazy to happen?
Here we go.
I'm gonna get ready with a bubble wand.
In case the door on the left or right opens and I need to be fast.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Is this it?
Cuckoo!
That's it?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Well, I saw the cuckoo come out.
What about the doors and the numbers?
And the five, two.
Well, shit, I'm out of here.
Out of here.
And then...
Where do we go?
Let's try and go...
Oh!
No.
Like, look at this whole dead space here.
It's all empty.
Where can we access from?
Oh!
Here!
Right there!
Look!
And that is...
F...
One?
Okay, let's really think about this, because this place is a goddamn nightmare.
There.
Uh...
So we go down.
We go right.
There's a phone.
We save.
And then we...
Go down.
Down again.
Turn right.
Oh yeah, there's also the slot business down there.
The slot business.
Oh, wait, wait, wait!
Oh no, that was a...
That's not the right way.
Not the right way.
Uh...
So I put question marks on the left.
Maybe it's actually easier...
If we come from that direction, over there.
Because that loops around, remember?
And the best way to get here...
Actually, there's no good way to get here.
This is a real pain.
Yeah, it looks like F1.
So here.
And this is the best way.
We gotta go down.
And we had to shoot this or something?
Beautiful.
Then at the very bottom...
Yeah.
Yep.
That is it.
And then...
Right.
Fuck!
No!
I hate this place.
So freaking much.
Okay.
You know what?
Fuck it.
I'm just gonna...
No!
I hate this place!
For fuck's sake!
I really do, man.
It's just...
Holy shit, I hate this place.
Come on.
Fucking...
You got this.
Okay, now what?
What do we do?
This way.
Jesus.
Right, you are gonna be really annoying, aren't you?
You're gonna be, uh...
If I...
Remote here, I'm gonna...
Wait.
Nah, I'm not doing that.
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna take my disc for a spin.
How about wait?
I can't come back.
Can I?
Hey!
Okay.
Huge.
Now we save the game!
Oh.
Yes.
Save the game.
Click on my buttons.
Nothing's happening?
Kinda wanna just, uh, re-explore this area just a little bit.
Just to see.
Right.
Uh...
No.
Down?
Oh no, this...
This place.
Uh...
No, I...
I wanna go further down.
This is not the plan.
Ah.
Doesn't matter.
Further down.
Here we go!
Oh!
We're gonna have, uh, company?
I mean...
What am I missing here?
Come on.
Like...
What do you want from me?
Huh?
Shit!
There's nothing I can do.
Actually, what...
What the fuck?
Like, what am I missing here?
I've seen multiple areas where there's a slot for something.
And I just don't know what to do.
Like, I don't need...
I have no...
idea!
Not the faintest.
Wait, why did I make a triangle down on the right?
I didn't connect it to anything.
Shit.
What's that?
This is my home.
Oh, you know what we could do?
We have a key, right?
There's other places where...
We can open a door, I think.
Let me see.
Look for question marks.
Uh, zoom out.
Is that a question mark?
It's not.
Why did I make an arrow there?
That seems... wrong.
There's a chest up here, apparently.
Bear 2...
Man.
Like, this is my problem with the game.
If you didn't mark something, when you found it the first time, you're pretty much fucked.
How on earth are you gonna figure out where the door was that needed a key?
Okay, I actually wrote key here.
But this is, like, of no significance, because...
This connects to something I've already...
Been to.
Needs EC?
What the fuck does that mean?
Electronic...
Countermeasures.
Uh...
Let's go to Bear 3.
I need to investigate what the hell is going on up here.
Yeah, it's Bear 3 time.
The 3 used of bears...
Are rearing their rares.
Rears.
Rares.
Rare rears.
Uh...
I don't know what I'm saying.
We go right.
It's this again.
So...
That.
Jump.
Yallabut.
Jallallabut.
Go!
I fucked it up!
Don't you just love it?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Back down.
Karkand!
Good.
Now, we go...
I have intimate, uh...
Knowledge of this place.
I had a bit of PTSD here, if you remember.
Let's head up and check that out, what I wrote there.
I wrote key.
I'm still salty about my key not working in my home.
Okay, so...
Why would I unlock this door?
That seems like a waste of a key.
Am I crazy?
I can just walk around.
Hello?
What?
Almost died.
You know, I...
I just go up...
Fuck!
I thought I had to be want.
I didn't.
Shit.
Oh, that's rough.
That hurts.
Come on.
There we go.
There.
Key circumvented.
The most useless door.
And what's the deal with this here?
With these five...
flapjacks.
They be flapping.
M-Disc Shrine.
Hey!
Would you look at that?
Look.
At the center.
Look at the concentric rings.
Okay?
Are you looking?
Now watch this.
Related?
Coincidence?
I think not.
Why did I say needs EC?
Needs...
Emergency contours.
Electronic...
I don't know.
Something.
Oh crap.
Let me check out the chest situation.
It's probably crazy.
Me when the chest situation is crazy.
Oh, let's go.
Oh, it's...
Already been looted.
Okay.
Well, in that case, I'm gonna remove the marker.
Cause that's just gonna confuse me.
Let me head up here now.
Thank you.
Oh!
Look at this!
Oh yeah!
Baby!
Wow!
I mean, I could have used that earlier.
Okay, here's the thing.
The fact that I can remove that disc up there...
Makes me think, maybe I need to bring it somewhere else now.
From a game design perspective, why else would you allow the player to take it back?
Right?
Oh!
Wait a minute now!
I think I understand what's happening, guys.
Remember the doors in the deep?
Drums in the deep?
With the evil face?
Maybe we gotta bring the evil creature there, and that will unlock the door.
You know?
Because those doors require biometric, uh, certification.
Which is only, uh...
Well...
Present in the evil creature.
But I'm also thinking of just exploring this pipe again.
Cause weren't there a couple places that we didn't get to...
Like this one!
Right there!
Like, what's going on there?
There!
That needs to be investigated.
Now that we blew a hole in the wall...
Maybe we can.
It's right before we reach the top, okay.
It should be right here?!
No!
Wait, what?
How did I just do that?!
I somehow broke my fall just now.
Save the game.
Hold on a minute.
How did I just do that?
If you're fast enough, the game doesn't register it?
Oh!
Look at...
You can do it downwards!
I didn't even know that!
Oh, that's so...
That's so good!
If you're falling?!
Holy shit, dude!
Oops!
Didn't mean to fall down here.
Oh, man!
That is such a nice feature.
Okay, so every time I fuck up, I can just sort of save it again.
Nice!
Man!
Fucking let me in.
What if I break your eggs?
Are you gonna be mad?
What is this totem pole here?
With a face on it?
Wait!
That's a happy face?
Check the thing.
Which happy face is it?
It's straight lines down and a smile.
Bottom.
It's almost like an O face.
You know, you go, oh!
With your mouth open?
But, uh...
Like, that is not...
Like, why is this here?
This is not a coincidence.
In a dedicated puzzle game, you can't just make stuff like that.
That has no meaning, right?
Like bubbles?
Okay.
Also, what's going on with this?
Like, that...
That is just...
Weird as hell, isn't it?
One, two, three, four, five...
Oh, oh!
Actually, this could be that type of mapping.
Meaning that...
This is the first sound, whatever it is.
Second, third, fourth, fifth, and so on.
So, if we somehow discover numbers...
Then we can, uh...
Translate the numbers into songs.
Let's say we discover six, seven, one, five, right?
Then we go, uh...
Six...
Seven...
One...
Five.
You see what I mean?
So, be on the lookout for...
I'm talking to myself here, of course.
Be on the lookout for...
Sequences of numbers.
Oh, wait!
Sequences of numbers?
Five, two!
Oh, whoops.
Five...
Two.
Five, two.
I probably have to do this near the clock.
What if...
Oh!
Ah, there's no...
But the clock is real-time.
I was about to say, what if I do the five at five o'clock?
And the two at two o'clock?
That would be the most insane puzzle ever.
And there's no way I would even want to do that.
That sounds ridiculous, if that's the case.
I kind of want to go back now.
How do I...
Is there like...
I wish there was a fast-travel melody to get back home.
Wait a minute.
Maybe there is.
Maybe the one in my room is a fast-travel melody.
Hold up.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight.
Eiffelry Pance bombing.
Damn it!
Okay.
So what is my best way home from now on?
I guess it is via the elevator, because now I have an easy axis, and if I fall, I can easily fix it.
It's a super easy way to get up there now.
It's not that hard.
Relatively speaking.
Compared to all other games, it is very hard.
But, you know.
Oh.
Just saying.
Also, can we not open this right here?
Wait a second.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Remember?
Okay, I had this theory that you needed to put a creature inside a wheel like this on these platforms.
I totally forgot I thought that.
We gotta somehow do that.
This is a rotational mechanism.
But where the hell do we do that and how?
I don't know.
We gotta figure it out.
Just keep going up.
And we get ready with the... with the bubles.
Love the bubles.
And we can even go further up now.
Yoink.
Oh.
Here.
And then we start from here.
Maybe... Oh!
Maybe I need to play the notes.
Uh...
Let's say the clock hits... Uh... What is the next it's gonna hit?
It's gonna be four o'clock, right?
So when it's four o'clock exactly during the cuckoo, cuckoo, I play the... the fourth note.
You see where I'm going with this?
But that's crazy.
That would mean I'd have to wait actual, like... hours.
That doesn't feel right, does it?
But we have 5-2.
Okay, so 5-2... is up.
I'm trying something.
Ah, I guess it would be between 1 and 2 if that... No, hold on.
That doesn't make any sense.
Uh...
5-2.
Maybe I played when... Hmm.
So we have a second minute and hour hand.
Okay, so wait a minute.
5-2.
Let's try that.
So when it reaches 2, we play 2.
And 2 was... That one.
Okay.
You ready?
And 5 was top.
5 was top.
Oh no, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm looking at the wrong one!
This is not the right one!
What the fuck am I doing?
This is the one!
5 is here!
2 is there!
Boop boop!
5, 2, 5, 2, 5... Come on!
Fuck!
Uh... Hmm.
5 on the left, 2 on the right.
This is not going well.
Please hang tight.
Hmm.
Let's try it when it's on 2.
We're gonna do 2.
And 2 was... Uh... Fuck, I can't read it.
2 is... You know, I should really put 1, 2... Oh wait, it's just the... Uh... I missed it!
I missed it!
Oh my god.
Wait.
5 is... 5 is... Left, 2 is down, right.
Whoops.
That's gotta...
Fuck!
5... 2...
Maybe it's like... Re... Rever... Maybe it's like 2, 5.
I am losing my god damn mind.
Why can't I open this door?
I got a key!
Also, you know what?
I should be taking notes on things like...
Uh... Hold on.
Let's just have like general...
notes.
Okay.
I need to find...
a key.
Let's make this a bit...
There we go.
Uh...
For my home...
Attic.
I guess...
Is what it is.
And then we also have...
Uh...
Find a...
Hamster wheel...
Thingy.
And...
Put it...
In...
Slot.
Then we have to do...
Uh...
What else?
Let me think.
Oh...
Uh...
Look for arrows...
To rescue...
The animals...
In cages.
It's like a general note...
Just to keep a look out for, right?
And...
Um...
Try...
5-2...
Uh...
At full hour...
On...
The clock.
Or...
At the clock.
Good.
And...
What else?
Uh...
Actually, I'm just gonna write this...
3...
4...
5...
6...
7...
8...
Maybe I need...
Oh, wait a second, actually.
Wait a...
Wait a god...
Damn...
Second.
This goes to 12, right?
Okay, this is gonna sound a little crazy, but...
What if...
No, no, nevermind, nevermind.
That's stupid.
Nevermind.
5...
What about this here?
Oh!
Wait a minute!
We gotta go back here and try this?
What?
Obviously!
The question is, where the fuck was that?
Uh, what did it look like?
Sort of like...
Blue area...
I don't even know what that animal is, but it has a beak.
It has a beak.
Where was that area?
See, this is...
This is gonna be impossible to find now.
Absolutely impossible.
I mean, the area looks blue, so I'm assuming it's gonna be here.
Have I seen that today at all?
I don't think so.
Okay, so...
The area with the cat is also blue, and the cat is here.
So it's probably nearby.
Also, the shape of the room is quite...
Rectanglish.
With a couple...
Little areas poking out on the right.
Let's look for that.
Rectangular room...
With areas poking out on the right.
That's rough.
Could be...
Any of these, man.
It's gonna be impossible to find.
I'm telling you.
That is an impossibility.
Dut, dut, dut, dut.
Click, clack, click, clack, click, clack, click, clack.
And what's with the zero, zero, zero?
Clickety, tickety-tock, goes the clock.
And this is a donut.
What if we scare it?
Oh my god, look.
The particles are being reflected in the donut.
It's choosing to reflect...
Some things...
And not other things.
Just like sphere.
If you know what I mean.
Hmm.
Ah, shit.
Man, this...
What is it with clocks in video games that I just can't grok?
You know?
It doesn't matter what video game it is.
If there's a clock, you better believe I won't solve that puzzle.
May as well go home.
Maybe the light reveals a secret here.
Or not.
Fuck!
And what about the...
Okay, hold on.
I actually have a theory about the skulls.
Check it out.
In fact, I'm gonna take a picture of it too while I'm there.
And you know what?
I'm also taking a picture of this fucking thing on the left, because trust me.
Trust me, there's something going on with that.
Uh...
Here.
Like, what the fuck is this?
Uh...
This... is a puzzle.
That's a combination somehow.
Wait a minute.
This is half...
Full?
Ah, but wait, now they alternate colors.
I'm trying to see if I can turn this into numbers.
Meaning...
Oh, I guess this would be...
Maybe I'm overthinking this.
Let's go to the skulls.
So, I'm pretty much gonna try to force as much as I can when it comes to, uh...
Extracting number sequences now, because I have a mapping.
So whenever I see anything that could potentially be a number sequence...
However...
Encrypted it is...
You better believe I'm gonna try and play that song for you.
The song of my people.
So even this right here...
Could be a number sequence.
Because think about it.
We have left...
We have...
Let me see...
Yeah, you can think about it.
Left, center, right.
Right?
But center, what note would that be?
If we're thinking in music.
I don't know.
There's also a number on each...
Oh!
No!
Wait!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7 skulls.
10 skulls.
11, 7, 10.
8, 8, 8.
6, 5, 3, 2.
The problem is I can't go that high...
With my...
With my music.
Shit.
Or can I?
Can I go that high?
What if we combine numbers somehow?
Can we add numbers?
No.
I don't think so.
There's also this...
Okay, that one can go away.
That's definitely not relevant anymore.
Neither are these arrows.
Or, you know what?
I'm gonna keep them.
Maybe there's like a puzzle at some point where you have to...
Do the whole sequence at once.
I can see that being a thing.
Let's take a picture of this as well.
Just to have it.
There.
Let's put it.
Could be a number...
Combination.
Somehow.
For the flute.
Put it over here, I guess.
Now.
What now?
Yeah.
I don't know.
I'm gonna stop it here.
It's been a long one anyway.
Almost five hours.
Oh wait.
22 minutes since last save.
We should probably go save.
Not that I think we did anything in those 22 minutes.
But you know.
Just to be safe.
Actually, even these...
What do you call it?
Bubbles in the air could be a number.
Or notes.
Actually.
If you think of notes in a...
The way you write music.
I don't know how to write or read music.
But I know there's like...
Heights of where you put them.
There's different lines.
That almost looks like something from Rain World.
That could be a note sequence.
Right there.
If you think about it.
I need to save the game.
Which was over here.
Yeah.
Okay.
27,870 steps.
Fif...
Oh yeah.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
I know I said it would stop.
It's the in-game time.
That's actually so helpful.
So I can keep track of it.
Nice.
Alright.
That was a good one.
Man.
There's actually so much in this game.
What the hell?
Isn't that crazy?
It's like a...
It doesn't feel like a long game at all.
Judging from the size of the map.
But dude.
It's super dense.
There's so much stuff on the map.
I found so many eggs today.
Yeah.
I did a lot.
That was very 6-7.
Do you guys know what I mean with a 6-7?
Or is it just Frank?
That's just like its map.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
There's so much in such a small space.
30 megabytes.
Yeah, that's...
By the way.
Insanity.
Yes, but stop.
You know what?
I'm gonna keep saying it now.
There's a YouTube video explaining it.
Ah, I know that.
There probably is.
I can probably also go on Know Your Meme and figure it out, but...
Oh, it's from a song?
Okay.
I got pretty far.
I beat the game today, actually.
Now I'm just sort of coasting.
I'm just chilling around the map and finding things.
I guess all of this right now is just sort of extra, which is cool.
My 14-year-old sister said it to my dad, and now they keep saying it for no reason in the family group.
That's so stupid.
What the hell?
Now it's eggie party hunting time?
Yeah, that's what I've been doing.
Pretty much.
And, you know, solving random puzzles.
But guys, is it any different?
I think it's just because we're old, you know?
Most of us here are old sacks, I think.
I mean, back when we were young, we used to say epic fail and shit.
You know, that's...
That's unheard of today to say.
You wouldn't say that today, right?
We used to say that shit back then.
That was cringe.
But we didn't know it.
Oh yeah, epic win as well.
Oh god.
It's horrible.
YOLO?
I think that one's still good.
I like saying YOLO.
MLG no-scope is still funny to me.
I also like the 360 crop rotation.
I don't know where it's from, but it's fucking hilarious.
Like, what even is that?
I like random humor.
I think it's funny.
That's why I like Eric Andre so much.
He's probably the funniest comedian that I've ever seen.
Maybe along with a Danish comedian called Anos Madison.
Who has one show that I have never laughed more at in my life.
He's kind of fallen off for me since then, but that one show...
Fucking kicked ass.
I couldn't breathe when I was watching that.
6-7 is just a...
Are you part of the in-crowd or not?
Ah, okay.
So if I want to reach the young people, I just go...
6-7, 6-7.
That's how you be...
That's how you like the guy...
What's up, fellow kids?
You know?
In Denmark, we say, uh...
We have ook med de unge.
We just like to say to be...
To be young with the young, you know?
Try to...
Fit in with the young people, I guess.
Yeah, how do you do, fellow kids?
That's the one.
Meep's kitten!
Gifting a bunch of subs again!
Thank you, man!
You have gifted 175 subs on this channel so far.
It's crazy.
Thank you.
Which Madison show?
I think it was called Ant & Venner To Be.
It's the one where he's talking about, uh...
The bakery.
Where he goes, uh...
Can I have that one?
NEIN!
Or something.
I can't say it.
It's also the one with the bunch.
Where they talk about eating brunch.
And it's like this week event.
That's so funny.
I think it's called Ant & Venner To Be.
But I'm not sure.
Yeah, staying hip.
How old am I?
I am...
33, I think?
I was born in 92.
Do the math.
Yeah, 30...
I'm definitely not 34.
I'm 33.
I'm an old gamer, man.
I'm gonna play a horror game after Animal Well.
I may even start it before I'm done with Animal Well.
Because I still want to do things in Animal Well.
I'm not done with this yet.
Even though I did reach credits.
I'm having fun just sort of unveiling things, you know?
I spent too much time watching you to justify not giving you and Twitch money.
You don't ever have to give me money, Meepskitten.
As long as you're watching, then that's cool.
I already earned some money via the ads that are being played, so...
Don't ever feel the need to donate money.
But I do appreciate it.
Thank you very much.
But don't ever feel like you're obligated to do it just because you're watching me.
Just you being here is way more than I could ask for.
You're doing very well in this game?
Oh.
Fuck, I thought you gave me a compliment and it's just a pun.
Ah.
You know what?
I'll take it as a compliment, though.
Ha ha ha ha.
It also hides ads for other viewers.
That is true, actually.
That's true.
That is true.
You're doing a good deed for other people when you do that, for sure.
Little Nightmares is a possibility.
But I was thinking about Amnesia, actually.
But for the next game on YouTube, I'm thinking perhaps...
I already gave sort of a hint in the Discord.
I haven't decided yet fully, but...
Those that follow the Discord may have seen some hints.
You also have some good emotes.
Not sure what to do with the channel point bonus.
Yeah, I need to really set something up with that.
I also have a bunch of slots for more emotes.
I don't know which ones I should put in, though.
Yeah, yeah, the bunker hive.
Someone gifted me the game some time ago, and I think it makes sense.
Was that the drip machine thing?
No, no, the drip machine is my coffee machine.
You guys were talking about me, or making fun of me for...
Drinking instant coffee?
Like a while ago?
But now I have a proper coffee machine, so I just wanted to chime in and say, Hey, I have a proper coffee machine now, just so you know.
You know?
Oh yeah, Jackie emote.
We should totally get that in.
Let me write it down, actually.
I wanted to put that in, but I forgot.
Okay.
Jackie's in.
You ever hear of streamer bot?
I feel like a nerd like you would adore it.
No, what is that?
Is it just a bot in the chat, like, stream elements or something?
I haven't heard of that.
We're funding your fancy life.
Yeah.
For sure.
Oh, the gym emote, that's a good one.
Let's do that one.
Maybe I can even make one where...
You know the cat emote where someone is petting the cat violently?
Giving it pats?
We can do the same hand, but for the gym emote.
Right?
Gym emote.
And Jackie emote.
That would be a good one.
Uh, let me see here.
Oh yeah, streamer bot.
Isn't it hella customizable?
I don't know.
Pet the mods.
That's a fun one.
Hey Oliver, can I recommend Home Safety Hotline as a game for the future?
Really short and neat.
Kinda horror themed, but definitely not a horror game.
That sounds interesting, actually.
Yes, you can.
I'mma add it to my backlog, actually.
While I have it here, otherwise I'll forget.
Let me see here.
Home...
What did you say?
Home Safety Hotline.
That sounds interesting.
Wait, it's not even on Backlogged.
Oh, it is.
It is.
Ah.
Interesting.
Analog horror inspired telephone operator simulator.
Holy mouthful.
That actually sounds kinda cool.
Okay, so it's an app you run locally that allows you to connect to Twitch OBS and many other services and create custom logic with visual programming or C Sharp.
I used to do some really neat things.
Oh shit, really?
I have not looked into that.
Let me actually write that down too.
I don't know anything about C Sharp though, but...
I can probably learn it.
And nowadays, with all the fucking AI chatbots, it should be easy to learn.
Streamer bots.
Can you make it your own hand?
It's just a gif of you pressing a button.
Maybe.
I...
That sounds like a hard thing to do, actually.
I don't know how I would do that.
For example, a channel point redeemed that runs custom code.
Ooh.
I mean, if you know how to program shit, you can practically do whatever, right?
The world is your oyster.
Hey, dumped soul.
That's a tragic username.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I just wanted to say I love your content.
I've been following this game actively while I'm watching your Subnautica playthrough passively.
Wait, what does that mean?
But, thanks.
You're watching one actively and watching one passively.
Interesting.
Is it like second monitor type stuff?
Because that's how I read it.
And that's cool.
I'm glad you like it.
ChatGPT can just do it for you?
Yeah, but...
I don't like just taking what it writes because...
It's not satisfying for me.
I kind of want to learn it at the same time.
So the way I use ChatGPT a lot with coding is like...
If there's like a new concept I didn't understand, I can just have like back and forth.
Keep asking questions.
And it's so good at that when it comes to coding.
It's really, really useful.
Any favorite soups?
Uh, probably potato soup is my favorite.
Good old potato soup.
But since it's Halloween, maybe I should make a nice pumpkin soup.
I make a spicy pumpkin soup with potatoes as well.
With like a Hokkaido pumpkin.
It's really tasty.
With chili and some cream.
Oh yeah.
And then you put bacon in there too.
If you want to make it extra nice.
I like my code in spaghetti and human made.
I mean, that is one way to do it.
Oh, you just had your wisdom tooth removed.
I would probably say...
A clear soup then or something.
Actually, any soup would be good for you.
Just, you know...
I mean, I like the rustic...
Down to earth soups, you know?
Like potato soup or tomato soup.
Stuff like that.
Simple stuff.
Pumpkin soup slaps.
Yeah, it does.
I don't have any ideas for a 100k special, guys.
I really don't.
Maybe I'll think of something.
Maybe it'll be a little delayed.
Actually, I have an idea for something.
But it's not really anything special.
It's just...
You'll see it when it happens.
If it happens.
Can you not control streamerbot with like Python or something?
Because I know how to code that and that's like my go-to.
Maybe there's like a wrapper for it.
Surely someone made it available in Python.
I don't know C-sharp, but actually I haven't ever used a C language.
Weren't you going to chop up the silver trophy in the end of five years?
Yeah, seven years.
Yeah.
It's going to happen.
I mean, if you think about it.
If the trophy is in my home, naturally over time it will be eroded by air.
And I will be breathing that.
So given enough million years, probably trillions, I don't know.
I will consume it.
Passively.
You can't do Python, but you'll get C-sharp pretty easy.
Okay, okay.
Gotcha.
Yeah, I haven't done anything with Java either yet.
Give it an assembly?
No thanks.
I'm not that much of a masochist.
See, that's something computers should be writing.
That's not meant for humans.
But it's kind of cool that humans have done it.
Very low level language.
Alright guys, I'm out of here.
I'm going to go eat something.
I don't know what though.
I've got to figure something out.
Maybe it'll just be good old rye bread with...
something on it.
I wish you a happy evening and...
yeah, thanks for watching.
I'll see you next time.
Bye bye.